5 WORDTAG I-MISC NETHERLANDS
5 WORDTAG O whales
10 WORDTAG O extra
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
5 WORDTAG O 83rd
6 WORDTAG O mind
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Roda
21 WORDTAG O 171
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Missionaries
19 WORDTAG O bad
9 WORDTAG O delivered
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Istanbul
7 WORDTAG O 47th
293 WORDTAG O year
10 WORDTAG O delay
439 WORDTAG O who
7 WORDTAG I-LOC WARSAW
6 WORDTAG I-MISC COUNTY
25 WORDTAG O 2-1
10 WORDTAG I-PER Armstrong
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Financial
5 WORDTAG O collision
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
35 WORDTAG O me
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Norwich
19 WORDTAG O verified
42 WORDTAG I-PER Lebed
13 WORDTAG I-PER Malik
52 WORDTAG I-ORG St
199 WORDTAG O new
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bridge
6 WORDTAG O reliever
5 WORDTAG O semifinalist
39 WORDTAG I-LOC Ukraine
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Senate
6 WORDTAG O District
5 WORDTAG O applications
25 WORDTAG O health
8 WORDTAG O task
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Swansea
71 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgium
48 WORDTAG I-MISC DIVISION
12 WORDTAG O ATHLETICS
18 WORDTAG O stop
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mohamed
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Roman
1496 WORDTAG O 's
7 WORDTAG I-PER Teutenberg
6 WORDTAG O briefing
47 WORDTAG I-PER Yeltsin
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
10 WORDTAG O effort
5 WORDTAG O partnership
8 WORDTAG O Date
6 WORDTAG O 1980s
8 WORDTAG I-PER Coetzer
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Press
5 WORDTAG O sports
38 WORDTAG O own
6 WORDTAG I-MISC KOREAN
14 WORDTAG O 504
9 WORDTAG O maybe
6 WORDTAG O Soccer
30 WORDTAG O estimated
6 WORDTAG O 1995/96
8 WORDTAG I-PER Pete
5 WORDTAG O procedure
10 WORDTAG O necessary
7 WORDTAG O street
5 WORDTAG O compromise
12 WORDTAG O minority
7 WORDTAG O occurred
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Ajax
13 WORDTAG O 61-2
9 WORDTAG O aid
8 WORDTAG O recovered
13 WORDTAG O four-day
7 WORDTAG O language
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Africa
8 WORDTAG O wait
18 WORDTAG O presidential
14 WORDTAG O enough
16 WORDTAG I-ORG CINCINNATI
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonds
5 WORDTAG O 93
687 WORDTAG O :
21 WORDTAG O negotiations
23 WORDTAG O firm
18 WORDTAG O secretary
55 WORDTAG O city
8 WORDTAG O prompt
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ischinger
6 WORDTAG I-PER Justin
106 WORDTAG O expected
11 WORDTAG O registration
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Partizan
7 WORDTAG I-PER Reeve
7 WORDTAG O Of
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Borussia
13 WORDTAG O raised
59 WORDTAG O 64
6 WORDTAG O 145
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Merrill
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Atletico
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hussein
16 WORDTAG O media
12 WORDTAG O father
37 WORDTAG O hold
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Wigan
14 WORDTAG O EPS
26 WORDTAG O tried
7 WORDTAG O Most
5 WORDTAG O bright
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Egyptian
15 WORDTAG O championships
9 WORDTAG O Following
5 WORDTAG O fours
17 WORDTAG O With
12 WORDTAG O immediate
18 WORDTAG O rounds
7 WORDTAG O Commissioner
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Syria
12 WORDTAG O cow
95 WORDTAG O 3.
5 WORDTAG I-PER Raichev
5 WORDTAG O 19th
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Airbus
10 WORDTAG O beaten
6 WORDTAG O oppose
22 WORDTAG O young
6 WORDTAG O acting
44 WORDTAG O return
18 WORDTAG O soldiers
12 WORDTAG I-PER Davis
20 WORDTAG O ethnic
29 WORDTAG O workers
53 WORDTAG O weekend
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Frenchman
6 WORDTAG O events
8 WORDTAG O produced
12 WORDTAG O thing
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayern
6 WORDTAG O getting
10 WORDTAG O 37
9 WORDTAG O According
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Texas
15 WORDTAG O ruled
121 WORDTAG O 1996-08-27
5 WORDTAG O showers
5 WORDTAG O roads
82 WORDTAG O tonnes
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chelsea
23 WORDTAG O 1991
19 WORDTAG O sides
106 WORDTAG O spokesman
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mubarak
7 WORDTAG O prix
5 WORDTAG O green
5 WORDTAG O voter
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Dayton
131 WORDTAG O AT
6 WORDTAG O 266
6 WORDTAG O PAY
9 WORDTAG O reduce
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Slough
7 WORDTAG I-PER K.
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Arnhem
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Telekom
40 WORDTAG O much
6 WORDTAG O develop
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Sydney
5 WORDTAG O surgeon
11 WORDTAG O scandal
9 WORDTAG I-PER Stefan
62 WORDTAG O same
9 WORDTAG O reduced
10 WORDTAG O spring
5 WORDTAG I-PER Stefano
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stenning
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arequipa
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kenneth
7 WORDTAG O confirm
8 WORDTAG O grade
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Unita
5 WORDTAG O TOTAL
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bielefeld
8 WORDTAG O idea
6 WORDTAG O seemed
216 WORDTAG O second
46 WORDTAG O DIVISION
10 WORDTAG O decide
20 WORDTAG I-LOC BONN
5 WORDTAG O commentary
13 WORDTAG O changed
5 WORDTAG O 1-106
6 WORDTAG O churches
46 WORDTAG O 26
9 WORDTAG O southeast
8 WORDTAG I-MISC HK$
8 WORDTAG O places
12 WORDTAG O defending
7 WORDTAG O column
22 WORDTAG O As
6 WORDTAG O deposed
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUDAPEST
8 WORDTAG I-LOC ANKARA
17 WORDTAG O adding
8 WORDTAG O eating
17 WORDTAG I-PER Wayne
7 WORDTAG O shots
5 WORDTAG O 416
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Royal
84 WORDTAG O half
5 WORDTAG O ordinary
5 WORDTAG O changing
23 WORDTAG O continued
13 WORDTAG O revised
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Japan
7 WORDTAG O chief-of-staff
9 WORDTAG O prepared
38 WORDTAG O On
52 WORDTAG O record
7 WORDTAG O putting
8 WORDTAG O serving
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Switzerland
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
7 WORDTAG O communist
20 WORDTAG O involved
15 WORDTAG O shooting
10 WORDTAG O employee
10 WORDTAG O crashed
16 WORDTAG O vouch
6 WORDTAG O Affairs
13 WORDTAG O cuts
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
8 WORDTAG O Eight
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Slovak
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbs
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Biogen
9 WORDTAG I-MISC DEM
37 WORDTAG O seen
9 WORDTAG O stopped
1846 WORDTAG O said
9 WORDTAG O fine
5 WORDTAG O effects
15 WORDTAG O THE
6 WORDTAG O retailer
11 WORDTAG O spent
314 WORDTAG O up
28 WORDTAG O force
12 WORDTAG O winners
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Birmingham
9 WORDTAG O 15,000
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dacom
6 WORDTAG O maker
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bordeaux
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Airways
51 WORDTAG O start
108 WORDTAG O she
35 WORDTAG O started
8 WORDTAG O Oct
20 WORDTAG O question
6 WORDTAG O difference
10 WORDTAG O 500
11 WORDTAG O Three
16 WORDTAG O entered
7 WORDTAG O explosives
5 WORDTAG I-MISC F
5 WORDTAG O .470
54 WORDTAG O leaders
536 WORDTAG O not
13 WORDTAG O Scores
5 WORDTAG I-PER Preston
155 WORDTAG O 8
56 WORDTAG O issue
109 WORDTAG O official
6 WORDTAG O mayor
8 WORDTAG O seedings
7 WORDTAG O improvement
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Seattle
12 WORDTAG I-PER Crawley
5 WORDTAG I-PER Albert
13 WORDTAG O finally
22 WORDTAG O problems
49 WORDTAG O those
24 WORDTAG O system
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ANGELES
13 WORDTAG I-LOC House
6 WORDTAG O SER
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurd
15 WORDTAG O others
11 WORDTAG O residents
80 WORDTAG O during
15 WORDTAG O beginning
18 WORDTAG O 35
7 WORDTAG O justice
5 WORDTAG O 941
7 WORDTAG O smaller
6 WORDTAG I-ORG LME
6 WORDTAG O ratio
41 WORDTAG I-MISC LEAGUE
15 WORDTAG O bat
22 WORDTAG O Some
84 WORDTAG O still
5 WORDTAG I-ORG NBH
55 WORDTAG O ended
32 WORDTAG O must
22 WORDTAG O chance
20 WORDTAG O summer
8 WORDTAG O advanced
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Power
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fredericks
13 WORDTAG O 6-
10 WORDTAG O powers
30 WORDTAG O *
14 WORDTAG O abroad
8 WORDTAG O FORECAST
29 WORDTAG I-ORG Ministry
29 WORDTAG O figures
16 WORDTAG I-ORG DETROIT
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frederic
21 WORDTAG I-LOC ENGLAND
7 WORDTAG O confessed
9 WORDTAG O receiving
22 WORDTAG O unit
44 WORDTAG O ...
17 WORDTAG O once
24 WORDTAG O less
9 WORDTAG O shipment
9 WORDTAG O especially
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Peace
7 WORDTAG I-PER Evert
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bossi
11 WORDTAG O expressed
24 WORDTAG O 77
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Brazilian
5 WORDTAG O 3.2
44 WORDTAG O parliament
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Rwandan
307 WORDTAG O I
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Santos
8 WORDTAG I-PER Juppe
25 WORDTAG O able
6 WORDTAG O unnamed
11 WORDTAG O judge
553 WORDTAG O it
5 WORDTAG O tested
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Foreign
8 WORDTAG I-PER Francisco
6 WORDTAG O sometimes
14 WORDTAG O large
14 WORDTAG O shareholders
5 WORDTAG O commitment
5 WORDTAG O swimming
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sudan
6 WORDTAG I-PER Vladimir
45 WORDTAG O election
31 WORDTAG O charges
9 WORDTAG O balance
5 WORDTAG O spying
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinians
5 WORDTAG O 4.4
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Nepal
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pot
8 WORDTAG O 54th
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Rwanda
5 WORDTAG O pinch-hitter
20 WORDTAG I-LOC The
19 WORDTAG O 1,000
5 WORDTAG O mining
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Grimsby
8 WORDTAG O link
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Moscow
5 WORDTAG O 1.2
11 WORDTAG O appear
23 WORDTAG O pounds
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JERUSALEM
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Padres
76 WORDTAG O game
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Guinea
18 WORDTAG O life
6 WORDTAG O protesters
10 WORDTAG O owns
15 WORDTAG O invited
6 WORDTAG O replacement
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Warwickshire
7 WORDTAG O PREMIER
9 WORDTAG I-PER Sarah
12 WORDTAG O employees
19 WORDTAG O midfielder
10 WORDTAG O calls
16 WORDTAG O 10,000
39 WORDTAG O nine
5 WORDTAG O BASKETBALL
19 WORDTAG I-LOC Oval
15 WORDTAG O provide
128 WORDTAG O played
18 WORDTAG O territory
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Stoke
21 WORDTAG O municipal
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Lodz
24 WORDTAG O bond
6 WORDTAG O magazine
16 WORDTAG O SCHEDULE
6 WORDTAG O bpd
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CAC-40
10 WORDTAG O fear
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ISS
21 WORDTAG O open
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
35 WORDTAG O long
7 WORDTAG O liquidity
16 WORDTAG O bus
5 WORDTAG O 4-95
32 WORDTAG O standings
8 WORDTAG O decree
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CALIFORNIA
5 WORDTAG O Gas
7 WORDTAG O overseas
32 WORDTAG O trying
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cedric
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brugge
25 WORDTAG O based
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gerhard
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Greek
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovakia
6 WORDTAG I-ORG VfB
12 WORDTAG O drop
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
13 WORDTAG I-PER Thorpe
27 WORDTAG O playing
5 WORDTAG O containing
11 WORDTAG I-PER Andre
11 WORDTAG O draft
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Hapoel
5 WORDTAG O Many
40 WORDTAG I-ORG U.N.
9 WORDTAG O .496
18 WORDTAG O feed
6 WORDTAG I-PER King
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Algeria
9 WORDTAG O determined
8 WORDTAG I-MISC NATIONAL
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
6 WORDTAG O explain
5 WORDTAG O subsidiary
9 WORDTAG O opportunity
18 WORDTAG O move
8 WORDTAG O confident
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Startup
13 WORDTAG O hurdles
8 WORDTAG I-PER Tapie
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Stansted
48 WORDTAG O office
23 WORDTAG O low
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Samsung
6 WORDTAG O die
5 WORDTAG O insisted
9 WORDTAG O inflation
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
25 WORDTAG O areas
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Schalke
51 WORDTAG O want
17 WORDTAG O qualifier
8 WORDTAG I-PER Petr
26 WORDTAG O position
6 WORDTAG O 202
17 WORDTAG O blamed
10 WORDTAG I-PER Jan
5 WORDTAG O ALERT
7 WORDTAG O regarding
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Basque
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamils
31 WORDTAG O death
9 WORDTAG O driving
22 WORDTAG O western
1093 WORDTAG O The
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Committee
6 WORDTAG O 2,000
5 WORDTAG O HRW
53 WORDTAG O near
7 WORDTAG O quality
9 WORDTAG O department
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Peru
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Holdings
11 WORDTAG I-PER Vicario
6 WORDTAG O attention
8 WORDTAG O SUMMARIES
260 WORDTAG O one
7 WORDTAG O PM
5 WORDTAG O experts
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ZIMBABWE
12 WORDTAG O reform
53 WORDTAG O security
2846 WORDTAG O (
8 WORDTAG O person
38 WORDTAG O previous
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Capital
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Venezuela
5 WORDTAG O container
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bochum
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tamil
83 WORDTAG O set
27 WORDTAG O violence
18 WORDTAG O paid
8 WORDTAG O firms
10 WORDTAG O project
10 WORDTAG O investigating
392 WORDTAG O 5
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Vitesse
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Arkansas
12 WORDTAG O something
19 WORDTAG O career
6 WORDTAG O mm
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
7 WORDTAG O firing
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrat
9 WORDTAG O reasons
8 WORDTAG I-ORG II
209 WORDTAG O He
6 WORDTAG O 64th
17 WORDTAG O terms
7 WORDTAG O 2001
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloucestershire
17 WORDTAG I-PER Russell
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Zealand
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Nigerian
5 WORDTAG O noon
5 WORDTAG I-PER Allen
17 WORDTAG I-ORG LOS
19 WORDTAG O car
18 WORDTAG O hand
5 WORDTAG I-ORG ministry
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Portsmouth
31 WORDTAG O coach
7 WORDTAG O forest
5 WORDTAG O 57th
5 WORDTAG I-PER Palkhivala
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nice
16 WORDTAG O diplomatic
9 WORDTAG O demanded
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rights
8 WORDTAG O blow
10 WORDTAG O care
15 WORDTAG O 49
14 WORDTAG I-PER Brown
112 WORDTAG O 15
44 WORDTAG O vs
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Niugini
9 WORDTAG O scientific
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Dortmund
20 WORDTAG O become
19 WORDTAG O traded
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bhutto
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sporting
8 WORDTAG O search
5 WORDTAG O edition
5 WORDTAG I-ORG OJ
5 WORDTAG I-PER Andreas
5 WORDTAG O 852
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sierra
99 WORDTAG O RESULTS
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
12 WORDTAG O history
50 WORDTAG O chief
7 WORDTAG I-LOC SEATTLE
14 WORDTAG O look
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lanusse
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Bosnian
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Thai
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Dutch
15 WORDTAG O mostly
5 WORDTAG O elsewhere
9 WORDTAG O SEP
11 WORDTAG O 8-6
6 WORDTAG I-PER Roberto
5 WORDTAG O aiming
6 WORDTAG O speaking
7 WORDTAG O consider
6 WORDTAG O box
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Ecuador
7 WORDTAG O addressed
85 WORDTAG O division
18 WORDTAG O key
9 WORDTAG I-PER der
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Metz
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Jamaica
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SBC
33 WORDTAG O children
17 WORDTAG O thought
13 WORDTAG O crime
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
7 WORDTAG O suspicion
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Elect
7 WORDTAG O attacked
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Freiburg
5 WORDTAG O sectors
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SEOUL
14 WORDTAG O ministers
10 WORDTAG O operations
54 WORDTAG O Women
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CLEVELAND
15 WORDTAG O boy
6 WORDTAG O allow
10 WORDTAG O jobs
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BOGOTA
52 WORDTAG O top
65 WORDTAG O 4.
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Indians
28 WORDTAG O pay
5 WORDTAG O caps
23 WORDTAG O seeded
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Kashmir
25 WORDTAG O civil
18 WORDTAG O rival
13 WORDTAG O lines
6 WORDTAG O majors
22 WORDTAG I-PER Johnson
8 WORDTAG O extradition
6 WORDTAG O affair
23 WORDTAG O fall
17 WORDTAG I-ORG BALTIMORE
8 WORDTAG I-PER Andy
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
9 WORDTAG O social
6 WORDTAG O ancient
5 WORDTAG O achieve
6 WORDTAG I-PER Juha
5 WORDTAG O restored
8 WORDTAG O headed
23 WORDTAG I-PER Steve
15 WORDTAG O am
21 WORDTAG O appeal
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangladesh
14 WORDTAG O Yellow
34 WORDTAG O production
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUCHAREST
7 WORDTAG O escape
7 WORDTAG O age
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ibrahim
220 WORDTAG O /
5 WORDTAG O taka
6 WORDTAG O forecasts
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Names
13 WORDTAG O nil
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Netherlands
17 WORDTAG O track
102 WORDTAG O them
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Morocco
14 WORDTAG I-ORG for
13 WORDTAG O conflict
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Afghan
26 WORDTAG O homer
14 WORDTAG O boat
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
23 WORDTAG O broke
10 WORDTAG I-PER Raymond
17 WORDTAG O losing
6 WORDTAG O scientists
5 WORDTAG O import
8 WORDTAG O possibility
8 WORDTAG O controllers
12 WORDTAG O recovery
17 WORDTAG O pair
33 WORDTAG O short
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
346 WORDTAG O are
11 WORDTAG O considered
7 WORDTAG O benefit
24 WORDTAG I-ORG EU
19 WORDTAG O 10th
5 WORDTAG O isolated
32 WORDTAG O stock
16 WORDTAG I-MISC CENTRAL
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Systems
67 WORDTAG I-LOC YORK
15 WORDTAG O travel
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Croatian
54 WORDTAG O tournament
5 WORDTAG O intercepted
3617 WORDTAG O of
45 WORDTAG I-MISC African
5 WORDTAG O recalled
5 WORDTAG O links
6 WORDTAG O provinces
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Winners
31 WORDTAG I-ORG European
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Office
14 WORDTAG I-PER Andrea
9 WORDTAG I-ORG MFS
10 WORDTAG O considering
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JOHANNESBURG
12 WORDTAG O While
11 WORDTAG O airports
22 WORDTAG I-PER Sohail
10 WORDTAG O SECOND
6 WORDTAG O arrests
9 WORDTAG O resolution
5 WORDTAG O breaking
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
7 WORDTAG O discussions
18 WORDTAG O defender
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Surrey
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
6 WORDTAG O gain
9 WORDTAG O outstanding
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Bradford
5 WORDTAG O legs
5 WORDTAG O plantation
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Graafschap
13 WORDTAG I-ORG The
8 WORDTAG O connection
5 WORDTAG O asking
41 WORDTAG O taken
32 WORDTAG O further
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Avonex
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Park
24 WORDTAG O break
15 WORDTAG O sex
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Yemen
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Toronto
10 WORDTAG O lending
7 WORDTAG O commercial
71 WORDTAG O can
21 WORDTAG O food
5 WORDTAG O contest
5 WORDTAG O CALL
8 WORDTAG O 13.
91 WORDTAG O billion
35 WORDTAG O manager
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
7 WORDTAG O **
15 WORDTAG I-ORG LOUIS
5 WORDTAG O criticised
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Beijing
5 WORDTAG O strikes
12 WORDTAG O 50,000
5 WORDTAG O pullout
46 WORDTAG O ahead
84 WORDTAG I-MISC German
5 WORDTAG O assistant
6 WORDTAG O critics
5 WORDTAG I-ORG PSG
93 WORDTAG I-PER Clinton
22 WORDTAG O banks
5 WORDTAG O fix
6 WORDTAG O global
9 WORDTAG O hitting
12 WORDTAG O Summary
38 WORDTAG O draw
9 WORDTAG O carried
10 WORDTAG O generally
5 WORDTAG O bulk
14 WORDTAG O 39
33 WORDTAG O 54
26 WORDTAG O south
5 WORDTAG O Up
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Taipei
282 WORDTAG O last
31 WORDTAG I-ORG Ltd
9 WORDTAG O federation
7 WORDTAG O owner
14 WORDTAG O Year
17 WORDTAG O deputy
15 WORDTAG O wounded
6 WORDTAG O killer
30 WORDTAG O private
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DHAKA
20 WORDTAG O weapons
13 WORDTAG I-LOC America
14 WORDTAG O unrest
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Wales
9 WORDTAG O slow
5 WORDTAG O supported
6 WORDTAG O Match
6 WORDTAG O UP
17 WORDTAG O development
8 WORDTAG O stores
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Jakarta
167 WORDTAG O 9
49 WORDTAG O allowed
7 WORDTAG O refugee
7 WORDTAG I-PER Luis
17 WORDTAG O seek
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BAGHDAD
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Cuban
45 WORDTAG O hours
6 WORDTAG O FROM
7 WORDTAG O everything
21 WORDTAG I-PER Teresa
14 WORDTAG O victims
8 WORDTAG O cleared
7 WORDTAG O 15th
11 WORDTAG O turn
5 WORDTAG O diesel
25 WORDTAG O aggregate
7 WORDTAG O NOTES
8 WORDTAG O stood
5 WORDTAG I-PER Strang
9 WORDTAG O guards
9 WORDTAG O lawsuit
5 WORDTAG O Fax
26 WORDTAG O met
11 WORDTAG O speaker
11 WORDTAG O promised
6 WORDTAG O kms
5 WORDTAG O pipes
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Wisconsin
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Baseball
5 WORDTAG O strongly
9 WORDTAG O field
5 WORDTAG O boats
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Aberdeen
6 WORDTAG O edge
8 WORDTAG O network
7 WORDTAG O review
16 WORDTAG I-LOC California
13 WORDTAG O book
40 WORDTAG O past
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
19 WORDTAG O For
18 WORDTAG O suffered
8 WORDTAG O abortion
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DUBAI
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bolton
70 WORDTAG O most
10 WORDTAG I-ORG the
13 WORDTAG O unq
9 WORDTAG O gone
13 WORDTAG O +31
10 WORDTAG O Other
6 WORDTAG O questions
15 WORDTAG O sought
19 WORDTAG O offered
15 WORDTAG I-ORG PHILADELPHIA
180 WORDTAG O about
6 WORDTAG I-PER Giles
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Saudi
169 WORDTAG O her
26 WORDTAG O know
7 WORDTAG O trouble
6 WORDTAG I-PER W.
75 WORDTAG O soccer
8 WORDTAG O transport
17 WORDTAG I-ORG KDP
6 WORDTAG I-PER Korda
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrats
15 WORDTAG O Second
6 WORDTAG O accuses
8 WORDTAG I-PER Collinelli
8 WORDTAG O doubt
29 WORDTAG I-PER Robert
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Nyva
13 WORDTAG O delivery
42 WORDTAG O asked
12 WORDTAG I-ORG LG
12 WORDTAG O evidence
346 WORDTAG O their
22 WORDTAG O radio
8 WORDTAG O AUG
21 WORDTAG O fire
12 WORDTAG I-PER Levy
20 WORDTAG O girls
5 WORDTAG O therapy
27 WORDTAG O today
35 WORDTAG O period
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Rangers
6 WORDTAG O vowed
11 WORDTAG O Both
9 WORDTAG O cycling
11 WORDTAG O cannot
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Sussex
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
5 WORDTAG O prisoners
6 WORDTAG O chains
11 WORDTAG O flew
5 WORDTAG O BY
17 WORDTAG O looked
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Yamaha
22 WORDTAG O 1992
5 WORDTAG O Chairman
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Korean
5 WORDTAG O aggressive
12 WORDTAG O funds
37 WORDTAG O again
6 WORDTAG O behalf
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Melbourne
64 WORDTAG O 6.
51 WORDTAG O miles
7 WORDTAG O newsdesk
13 WORDTAG I-LOC TORONTO
17 WORDTAG O one-day
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
5 WORDTAG O loans
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Berlin
236 WORDTAG O against
7 WORDTAG I-PER Colonna
1 WORDTAG B-MISC _RARE_
9 WORDTAG O coast
5 WORDTAG O painted
6 WORDTAG O concrete
8 WORDTAG I-ORG RKC
52 WORDTAG O Attendance
6 WORDTAG O airliner
6 WORDTAG O renewed
13 WORDTAG I-PER White
5 WORDTAG I-PER God
6 WORDTAG I-PER Zhirinovsky
23 WORDTAG O talk
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Willem
6 WORDTAG O pilot
12 WORDTAG O assault
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
26 WORDTAG O 'S
9 WORDTAG O planning
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
5 WORDTAG O Interior
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Spartak
6 WORDTAG O retain
75 WORDTAG O minutes
5 WORDTAG O nominated
5 WORDTAG O rubber
6 WORDTAG O surge
9 WORDTAG O 4-2
17 WORDTAG O More
18 WORDTAG O management
19 WORDTAG O allowing
7 WORDTAG O allocated
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ETA
19 WORDTAG O overnight
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Edouard
6 WORDTAG O 111
9 WORDTAG O established
15 WORDTAG O followed
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cubs
10 WORDTAG O longer
12 WORDTAG I-PER Stephen
12 WORDTAG O cattle
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kornblum
21 WORDTAG I-PER Lewis
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Revolutionary
8 WORDTAG O lived
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Escort
46 WORDTAG O may
7 WORDTAG O doctor
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
18 WORDTAG O positive
220 WORDTAG O when
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cofinec
6 WORDTAG O franc
5 WORDTAG I-MISC East
14 WORDTAG O unchanged
5 WORDTAG I-PER Drew
6 WORDTAG I-ORG MSV
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Petroleum
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fischler
5 WORDTAG O bureau
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Detroit
85 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistan
20 WORDTAG O expect
29 WORDTAG I-ORG SAN
28 WORDTAG I-PER Younis
5 WORDTAG O boxcar
11 WORDTAG O organisers
7 WORDTAG O revenues
24 WORDTAG O DIGEST
8 WORDTAG O absence
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Prize
36 WORDTAG I-PER Dutroux
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Spaniard
10 WORDTAG O Traders
85 WORDTAG O news
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BELGRADE
40 WORDTAG O signed
7 WORDTAG O Princess
42 WORDTAG O head
5 WORDTAG O communications
5 WORDTAG I-PER Goran
5 WORDTAG O posts
10 WORDTAG O ran
10 WORDTAG O suspects
6 WORDTAG I-PER Abdul
8 WORDTAG O proposals
18 WORDTAG O 81
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Crystal
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Tilburg
10 WORDTAG O wrote
6 WORDTAG O 56th
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Kuwait
16 WORDTAG O books
9 WORDTAG I-PER Davies
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jayasuriya
16 WORDTAG I-ORG BOSTON
9 WORDTAG O dollars
6 WORDTAG O 200,000
6 WORDTAG I-MISC S.
25 WORDTAG O 45
37 WORDTAG O PCT
109 WORDTAG O former
11 WORDTAG I-ORG South
10 WORDTAG O All
6 WORDTAG O 116
23 WORDTAG O compared
6 WORDTAG O picture
55 WORDTAG O minister
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lloyd
18 WORDTAG O stated
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Costa
13 WORDTAG O imports
20 WORDTAG O domestic
11 WORDTAG O written
5 WORDTAG O tunnel
16 WORDTAG I-PER Stewart
8 WORDTAG O conducted
5 WORDTAG O apiece
5 WORDTAG I-ORG IMED
12 WORDTAG O score
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pires
16 WORDTAG O biggest
108 WORDTAG O home
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sachs
35 WORDTAG O least
9 WORDTAG O homered
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Liberation
5 WORDTAG O platform
8 WORDTAG O magazines
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Sierra
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Geneva
47 WORDTAG O 28
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
73 WORDTAG O results
6 WORDTAG O fighters
6 WORDTAG O rainfall
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Taiwan
8 WORDTAG I-ORG McLaren
8 WORDTAG O negative
5 WORDTAG O Doctors
5 WORDTAG O climb
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Singer
14 WORDTAG I-LOC KONG
9 WORDTAG O counterpart
20 WORDTAG O mark
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Sparta
8 WORDTAG O lunch
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chorzow
8 WORDTAG I-PER Javier
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Leicester
258 WORDTAG O government
8 WORDTAG O homers
85 WORDTAG O 1996-08-25
13 WORDTAG O 800
67 WORDTAG O minute
28 WORDTAG I-ORG PSV
56 WORDTAG O behind
24 WORDTAG O LEAGUE
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jason
114 WORDTAG O 21
35 WORDTAG O champions
105 WORDTAG O 70
10 WORDTAG O speculation
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Diego
5 WORDTAG O settlements
47 WORDTAG O km
98 WORDTAG I-LOC Italy
9 WORDTAG O About
52 WORDTAG O players
5 WORDTAG I-PER Herbert
5 WORDTAG O Q2
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbert
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Front
6 WORDTAG O involves
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Anyang
14 WORDTAG O parliamentary
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sauber
5 WORDTAG O filled
12 WORDTAG O weather
171 WORDTAG O In
7 WORDTAG I-PER Barbara
8 WORDTAG I-PER Davenport
22 WORDTAG O increase
18 WORDTAG O sources
73 WORDTAG I-LOC NEW
5 WORDTAG I-PER Headley
75 WORDTAG O lead
6 WORDTAG O Analysts
30 WORDTAG O likely
7 WORDTAG I-PER Volkova
48 WORDTAG O several
2846 WORDTAG O )
24 WORDTAG O according
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Volendam
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magdalena
6 WORDTAG O mountain
36 WORDTAG O give
5 WORDTAG O 389
7 WORDTAG O finding
5 WORDTAG O prayer
212 WORDTAG O Tuesday
12 WORDTAG I-PER Tsang
23 WORDTAG O never
13 WORDTAG O handed
14 WORDTAG O noted
6 WORDTAG O related
11 WORDTAG O using
9 WORDTAG O THIRD
66 WORDTAG O 1996-08-24
43 WORDTAG O went
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Berlex
10 WORDTAG O effective
30 WORDTAG O date
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Celica
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Brewers
47 WORDTAG I-PER Arafat
25 WORDTAG I-PER Khan
8 WORDTAG O produce
15 WORDTAG O nothing
5 WORDTAG O paedophile
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Western
10 WORDTAG O 5000
10 WORDTAG O clearly
14 WORDTAG I-ORG DIEGO
16 WORDTAG O event
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Lille
13 WORDTAG O pressure
23 WORDTAG O 326
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Chechen
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Nantes
19 WORDTAG O sixth
6 WORDTAG O climbed
49 WORDTAG I-ORG New
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Melbourne
5 WORDTAG I-LOC St
33 WORDTAG O 10.
14 WORDTAG I-PER Daniel
5 WORDTAG O kerosene
30 WORDTAG O small
45 WORDTAG O reporters
6 WORDTAG O neither
13 WORDTAG O unable
11 WORDTAG O friendly
18 WORDTAG O truck
12 WORDTAG O customs
105 WORDTAG O statement
13 WORDTAG I-PER Banharn
7 WORDTAG O weight
7 WORDTAG I-MISC CHAMPIONSHIP
11 WORDTAG O violations
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Algiers
8 WORDTAG I-PER Brian
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Nicaraguan
13 WORDTAG I-ORG ,
7 WORDTAG O class
7 WORDTAG O reserves
9 WORDTAG O base
7 WORDTAG O signs
12 WORDTAG I-PER Inzamam-ul-Haq
9 WORDTAG O makes
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Florida
19 WORDTAG O 've
40 WORDTAG O hits
95 WORDTAG I-LOC New
22 WORDTAG I-PER Ian
71 WORDTAG I-MISC Open
9 WORDTAG O 125
15 WORDTAG O giving
12 WORDTAG O bit
23 WORDTAG O house
10 WORDTAG I-PER Maskhadov
50 WORDTAG O 8.
7 WORDTAG O labour
12 WORDTAG O Although
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Paris
29 WORDTAG O policy
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Germain
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Mariners
133 WORDTAG I-LOC Britain
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rapid
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pioline
42 WORDTAG O few
5 WORDTAG O aide
8 WORDTAG O noise
17 WORDTAG O form
6 WORDTAG O supporters
5 WORDTAG I-PER Howard
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Latvia
86 WORDTAG O June
81 WORDTAG O now
10 WORDTAG O opens
8 WORDTAG O scene
7 WORDTAG O faced
5 WORDTAG O perhaps
20 WORDTAG I-MISC CUP
67 WORDTAG I-MISC French
6 WORDTAG O qualified
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kim
9 WORDTAG O prompted
54 WORDTAG O report
9 WORDTAG O document
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Dundee
8 WORDTAG O RACING
6 WORDTAG O pleased
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Auckland
5 WORDTAG O parents
10 WORDTAG O fraud
37 WORDTAG O these
37 WORDTAG O 9.
5 WORDTAG O cold
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ford
5 WORDTAG O narrow
22 WORDTAG O far
201 WORDTAG O three
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Somerset
22 WORDTAG O ninth
65 WORDTAG O league
24 WORDTAG O 2-6
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joseph
61 WORDTAG O run
28 WORDTAG I-PER Croft
11 WORDTAG O mixed
18 WORDTAG I-PER Bob
100 WORDTAG O world
6 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-led
8 WORDTAG O manage
21 WORDTAG O traders
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Banespa
11 WORDTAG O feet
5 WORDTAG O roubles
5 WORDTAG I-PER Phan
21 WORDTAG O 34
5 WORDTAG O everyone
38 WORDTAG O campaign
12 WORDTAG O questioned
16 WORDTAG O feel
10 WORDTAG O vice
19 WORDTAG O rest
7 WORDTAG O popular
5 WORDTAG O membership
6 WORDTAG O kilometre
25 WORDTAG O kept
6 WORDTAG B-ORG Greens
13 WORDTAG O picked
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Wall
62 WORDTAG O go
10 WORDTAG O clocked
12 WORDTAG O opinion
37 WORDTAG O high
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Auxerre
5 WORDTAG O 107
5 WORDTAG O listed
47 WORDTAG O television
29 WORDTAG O 61
8 WORDTAG O militia
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cardiff
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Heerenveen
6 WORDTAG O Security
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Gencor
5 WORDTAG O shelling
5 WORDTAG O provided
5 WORDTAG O letters
5 WORDTAG O By
31 WORDTAG O clear
14 WORDTAG I-ORG PITTSBURGH
16 WORDTAG O measures
6 WORDTAG O nun
60 WORDTAG O called
24 WORDTAG O director
27 WORDTAG O TO
36 WORDTAG O wickets
7 WORDTAG O selling
10 WORDTAG O advertising
18 WORDTAG O debt
5 WORDTAG I-LOC AIRES
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Marlins
5 WORDTAG O placed
13 WORDTAG O speak
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Rica
5 WORDTAG O ranked
58 WORDTAG O put
5 WORDTAG O routine
21 WORDTAG I-PER Jim
7 WORDTAG O FINAL
12 WORDTAG O 15-6
33 WORDTAG O given
26 WORDTAG O charged
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Worcestershire
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mia
25 WORDTAG O centre
20 WORDTAG O overall
19 WORDTAG O 43
7 WORDTAG O wounds
8 WORDTAG O king
10 WORDTAG O star
14 WORDTAG O C
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
11 WORDTAG O fishermen
14 WORDTAG O filed
5 WORDTAG O ONE-DAY
9 WORDTAG O 95
20 WORDTAG O value
23 WORDTAG O 32
7 WORDTAG O hundreds
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nathalie
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
5 WORDTAG O 555
29 WORDTAG O level
8 WORDTAG O autonomy
13 WORDTAG O wins
6 WORDTAG O education
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fernandez
9 WORDTAG O standing
8 WORDTAG O Amount
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trafford
13 WORDTAG O imposed
10 WORDTAG I-LOC UK
14 WORDTAG O banned
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Croatia
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bristol
84 WORDTAG O metres
144 WORDTAG O than
24 WORDTAG O penalty
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
11 WORDTAG O status
6 WORDTAG O terrorist
7 WORDTAG O greatest
7 WORDTAG O signing
9 WORDTAG I-PER Smicer
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Zimbabwe
5 WORDTAG I-PER Boer
15 WORDTAG O joined
13 WORDTAG O wants
5 WORDTAG O 1-2
7 WORDTAG O amount
8 WORDTAG I-PER Kevorkian
17 WORDTAG I-PER Anwar
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamic
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Benfica
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Liberia
6 WORDTAG O express
5 WORDTAG O investments
75 WORDTAG O early
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Corsica
7 WORDTAG O installed
7 WORDTAG O 3311812-4
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Leduc
10 WORDTAG O read
19 WORDTAG I-LOC City
16 WORDTAG O things
5 WORDTAG O camps
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
6 WORDTAG I-PER Hope
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
16 WORDTAG O majority
6 WORDTAG O 7.0
23 WORDTAG O carrying
9 WORDTAG O college
35 WORDTAG O 29
26 WORDTAG O convention
9 WORDTAG O meetings
25 WORDTAG I-ORG OSCE
6 WORDTAG O limits
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erik
11 WORDTAG O means
25 WORDTAG O outside
10 WORDTAG I-PER Max
59 WORDTAG O singles
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mauritius
26 WORDTAG O comment
6 WORDTAG O seriously
6 WORDTAG I-PER Cyprien
27 WORDTAG O coming
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
24 WORDTAG I-LOC Jordan
5 WORDTAG O friends
5 WORDTAG O acres
65 WORDTAG O play
6 WORDTAG O garlic
9 WORDTAG O Qualifier
5 WORDTAG O offering
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ICAC
8 WORDTAG I-MISC AMERICAN
8 WORDTAG O showing
7 WORDTAG I-LOC JAKARTA
5 WORDTAG O marijuana
28 WORDTAG O sold
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Netherlands
6 WORDTAG O suspension
7 WORDTAG O plants
6 WORDTAG O finals
5 WORDTAG I-ORG League
8 WORDTAG I-PER Mika
9 WORDTAG O jet
8 WORDTAG O bring
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
5 WORDTAG I-PER Moxon
6 WORDTAG O personal
7 WORDTAG O ask
198 WORDTAG O A
10 WORDTAG O provincial
50 WORDTAG O court
13 WORDTAG O interview
3390 WORDTAG O in
31 WORDTAG O industry
7 WORDTAG O 109
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sharpe
9 WORDTAG O 1996/97
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Workers
15 WORDTAG I-LOC TOKYO
44 WORDTAG O 1994
6 WORDTAG O leftist
5 WORDTAG O save
13 WORDTAG O ruling
5 WORDTAG O reluctant
15 WORDTAG O State
20 WORDTAG O 200
11 WORDTAG I-PER Adrian
18 WORDTAG O bln
6 WORDTAG O intent
54 WORDTAG O rebels
6 WORDTAG O northeast
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fowler
14 WORDTAG O performance
86 WORDTAG O 30
21 WORDTAG O rain
416 WORDTAG O will
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Burundi
8 WORDTAG O skull
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Moody
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Democracy
31 WORDTAG I-MISC Democratic
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Toyota
20 WORDTAG O movement
45 WORDTAG O loss
25 WORDTAG O wheat
8 WORDTAG O maintain
11 WORDTAG O 199
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Authority
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Stock
6 WORDTAG O taxes
5 WORDTAG O fields
11 WORDTAG O includes
7 WORDTAG O pretty
10 WORDTAG O worst
9 WORDTAG O executed
27 WORDTAG O chairman
6 WORDTAG O acquired
55 WORDTAG O 16
12 WORDTAG O moved
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Eritrea
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Daewoo
5 WORDTAG O A-rated
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Moldova
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Chelsea
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Rabobank
76 WORDTAG I-LOC South
6 WORDTAG O politician
5 WORDTAG O warning
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperation
5 WORDTAG O pesetas
6 WORDTAG O exile
44 WORDTAG O night
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Interfax
15 WORDTAG O slightly
82 WORDTAG O killed
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
42 WORDTAG O morning
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lloyd
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Globo
5 WORDTAG O cool
192 WORDTAG O Monday
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Amsterdam
24 WORDTAG O step
6 WORDTAG O irregularities
5 WORDTAG I-PER Blind
94 WORDTAG O 1.
5 WORDTAG O barred
16 WORDTAG I-MISC EASTERN
8 WORDTAG I-PER Christian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Necmettin
11 WORDTAG O 7-1
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Paris
10 WORDTAG O pts
15 WORDTAG I-ORG /
19 WORDTAG O options
6 WORDTAG O boosted
14 WORDTAG O role
16 WORDTAG O common
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Montpellier
16 WORDTAG O basis
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Reserve
8 WORDTAG O blast
6 WORDTAG O intended
60 WORDTAG O then
757 WORDTAG O from
10 WORDTAG I-PER Norman
28 WORDTAG O prison
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Albania
13 WORDTAG O include
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aoki
9 WORDTAG O Final
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Information
36 WORDTAG O released
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Baltimore
7 WORDTAG O refunds
45 WORDTAG O 19
7 WORDTAG O closes
81 WORDTAG O season
14 WORDTAG O introduced
22 WORDTAG O These
11 WORDTAG O Shares
7 WORDTAG O formally
5 WORDTAG O settle
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonan
6 WORDTAG O civilians
7 WORDTAG O railway
27 WORDTAG O within
15 WORDTAG O looking
11 WORDTAG O servants
7 WORDTAG O camp
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gatwick
5 WORDTAG O associated
17 WORDTAG O arrest
8 WORDTAG O plus
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Advanced
6 WORDTAG O cover
5 WORDTAG O scoreless
48 WORDTAG O women
11 WORDTAG O militants
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
6 WORDTAG O 5-1
6 WORDTAG O invitation
7 WORDTAG O secured
6 WORDTAG I-PER Yassin
7 WORDTAG O Playing
5 WORDTAG O style
26 WORDTAG O keep
13 WORDTAG O account
8 WORDTAG I-PER Derek
6 WORDTAG O located
20 WORDTAG O union
28 WORDTAG O No
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
5 WORDTAG O clause
27 WORDTAG O confirmed
19 WORDTAG I-ORG FC
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Heathrow
5 WORDTAG I-PER Nilis
5 WORDTAG O bases
8 WORDTAG O emerged
6 WORDTAG O Aggregate
5 WORDTAG O pass
7 WORDTAG O regions
5 WORDTAG O follow
6 WORDTAG O operate
6 WORDTAG O 180
7 WORDTAG O choice
10 WORDTAG O lifted
7 WORDTAG O RECORD
6 WORDTAG I-PER An
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sakigake
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp.
6 WORDTAG O stand
14 WORDTAG O rupiah
19 WORDTAG O wanted
6 WORDTAG O arriving
12 WORDTAG O site
23 WORDTAG O single
6 WORDTAG O citizen
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Baltimore
20 WORDTAG O quiet
5 WORDTAG I-PER Veldman
86 WORDTAG O meeting
46 WORDTAG O later
6 WORDTAG O confiscated
6 WORDTAG O makers
24 WORDTAG O leave
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Tigers
5 WORDTAG O model
5 WORDTAG O bushel
6 WORDTAG I-PER Capiot
10 WORDTAG O 110
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamists
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fogarty
5 WORDTAG I-PER Dick
9 WORDTAG O cross
6 WORDTAG O affairs
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Argentina
33 WORDTAG O shot
5 WORDTAG O 4221
49 WORDTAG O demand
14 WORDTAG O veteran
840 WORDTAG O with
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bastia
8 WORDTAG O bed
37 WORDTAG O ---
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
8 WORDTAG O first-round
18 WORDTAG I-PER Saeed
25 WORDTAG O percentage
22 WORDTAG O 3-6
7 WORDTAG O kick
5 WORDTAG O 8520
10 WORDTAG I-PER Colin
10 WORDTAG O finish
8 WORDTAG O candidates
6 WORDTAG O jewelry
5 WORDTAG O reigning
10 WORDTAG O study
17 WORDTAG O visited
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ABC
5 WORDTAG O riders
29 WORDTAG O better
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephanie
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Zurich
5 WORDTAG O effectively
6 WORDTAG O incidents
7 WORDTAG O agenda
12 WORDTAG O candidate
9 WORDTAG O conservative
10 WORDTAG O certain
46 WORDTAG O men
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Paulo
7 WORDTAG I-PER Lindsay
5 WORDTAG O STAGE
9 WORDTAG O GOLF
9 WORDTAG O version
23 WORDTAG O lot
6 WORDTAG O renegade
122 WORDTAG O round
17 WORDTAG O church
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ulihrach
67 WORDTAG O our
7 WORDTAG I-LOC ATLANTA
7 WORDTAG O Its
57 WORDTAG O rate
11 WORDTAG I-PER Simon
16 WORDTAG I-ORG SEATTLE
15 WORDTAG I-ORG COLORADO
47 WORDTAG O championship
6 WORDTAG O sound
11 WORDTAG O hostage
6 WORDTAG O forcing
5 WORDTAG O seems
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dennis
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Arab
2994 WORDTAG O a
8 WORDTAG O cotton
5 WORDTAG O 6.5
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Uganda
59 WORDTAG O prices
9 WORDTAG O vehicle
271 WORDTAG O over
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Arsenal
12 WORDTAG O debut
6 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neill
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Northamptonshire
15 WORDTAG O wicket
7 WORDTAG O possibly
31 WORDTAG O rates
8 WORDTAG I-ORG RUGBY
26 WORDTAG O 55
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Supreme
6 WORDTAG O refined
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
6 WORDTAG O wo
5 WORDTAG O contacts
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Republicans
6 WORDTAG O 14.
37 WORDTAG O future
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bohdan
14 WORDTAG O 3-1
6 WORDTAG O rider
7 WORDTAG O founded
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Series
21 WORDTAG O plant
12 WORDTAG O soldier
16 WORDTAG O General
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cea
6 WORDTAG I-ORG China
7 WORDTAG O restaurant
68 WORDTAG I-LOC Iraq
12 WORDTAG O long-term
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Reds
6 WORDTAG O highway
8 WORDTAG O rare
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Amman
6 WORDTAG O tourist
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yankees
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dodgers
14 WORDTAG I-PER George
102 WORDTAG O lost
19 WORDTAG I-ORG Democratic
6 WORDTAG O bombing
131 WORDTAG O '
14 WORDTAG O +44
6 WORDTAG O yield
6 WORDTAG O 88
6 WORDTAG I-PER Miller
7 WORDTAG O 120
79 WORDTAG I-ORG Reuters
25 WORDTAG O poor
12 WORDTAG O software
75 WORDTAG O innings
12 WORDTAG O managed
14 WORDTAG I-PER Greg
8 WORDTAG O animal
38 WORDTAG O region
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Los
10 WORDTAG O growing
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Haitai
31 WORDTAG O woman
43 WORDTAG O power
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Cincinnati
15 WORDTAG I-PER Ijaz
9 WORDTAG O visiting
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sosa
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Swindon
9 WORDTAG O yuan
26 WORDTAG O services
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Post
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SOFIA
8 WORDTAG O tension
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alami
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Headingley
7 WORDTAG O foreigners
9 WORDTAG O three-game
20 WORDTAG O included
17 WORDTAG O largest
6 WORDTAG O 86th
56 WORDTAG O months
5 WORDTAG O wells
18 WORDTAG O dealer
6 WORDTAG O affect
5 WORDTAG I-PER Lamm
5 WORDTAG O 1948
7 WORDTAG O attending
9 WORDTAG O republic
12 WORDTAG I-ORG OB
13 WORDTAG O numbers
5 WORDTAG O 181
9 WORDTAG I-PER Philip
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Krakow
7 WORDTAG O transition
25 WORDTAG O change
37 WORDTAG O control
6 WORDTAG O kidnappers
9 WORDTAG O collided
7 WORDTAG O reveal
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BRASILIA
5 WORDTAG O stockpile
7 WORDTAG O truth
9 WORDTAG O someone
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Dinamo
11 WORDTAG O streets
10 WORDTAG O jailed
17 WORDTAG O 1-6
5 WORDTAG I-ORG People
5 WORDTAG O pace
112 WORDTAG O five
11 WORDTAG O request
28 WORDTAG O earnings
18 WORDTAG O doing
95 WORDTAG O 2.
25 WORDTAG O island
5 WORDTAG O tree
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Japanese
7 WORDTAG O timetable
76 WORDTAG O took
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Giants
17 WORDTAG O landed
15 WORDTAG O heart
6 WORDTAG O itself
6 WORDTAG O controversial
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
14 WORDTAG O activity
6 WORDTAG O becoming
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mitchell
13 WORDTAG O convicted
71 WORDTAG I-LOC India
32 WORDTAG O 96
37 WORDTAG O working
6 WORDTAG I-PER McEwen
7 WORDTAG O strikeouts
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Warsaw
6 WORDTAG O disarmament
17 WORDTAG I-ORG News
37 WORDTAG O cash
7 WORDTAG O cent
23 WORDTAG O whose
30 WORDTAG O old
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sao
8 WORDTAG O snap
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ruch
5 WORDTAG O require
9 WORDTAG O partner
9 WORDTAG I-PER Enqvist
5 WORDTAG O boycott
103 WORDTAG O 1996-08-23
8 WORDTAG O rivals
5 WORDTAG O BP
37 WORDTAG I-PER Akram
16 WORDTAG I-MISC GERMAN
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Congress
6 WORDTAG O maximum
6 WORDTAG O sentiment
55 WORDTAG O opposition
9 WORDTAG I-PER Campbell
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jens
21 WORDTAG O hijackers
42 WORDTAG O oil
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Sudan
5 WORDTAG O preferred
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Indonesian
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Securities
6 WORDTAG O fails
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mickelson
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
8 WORDTAG O treated
9 WORDTAG O 1996-08-30
11 WORDTAG I-PER Frank
15 WORDTAG O driver
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kevin
349 WORDTAG O two
5 WORDTAG O intends
25 WORDTAG O continue
11 WORDTAG O takes
716 WORDTAG O by
6 WORDTAG O offset
5 WORDTAG O laps
100 WORDTAG O 6-2
11 WORDTAG I-PER James
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Nikkei
5 WORDTAG O businessman
8 WORDTAG O Her
8 WORDTAG O systems
11 WORDTAG O previously
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lincoln
17 WORDTAG O 1993
29 WORDTAG O captain
45 WORDTAG O came
25 WORDTAG O even
5 WORDTAG O 220
15 WORDTAG O moment
24 WORDTAG I-MISC Turkish
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nijmegen
6 WORDTAG O multiple
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhaka
20 WORDTAG O mission
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fairbrother
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventus
16 WORDTAG O building
5 WORDTAG O Queen
1418 WORDTAG O 1
34 WORDTAG I-LOC Chechnya
18 WORDTAG O post
5 WORDTAG O imprisonment
6 WORDTAG O increasing
5 WORDTAG O autumn
18 WORDTAG O sale
32 WORDTAG O If
15 WORDTAG O presence
100 WORDTAG O 20
6 WORDTAG I-LOC S.
7 WORDTAG O 112
6 WORDTAG O PRICE
7 WORDTAG I-MISC BELGIAN
20 WORDTAG I-LOC PAKISTAN
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southern
6 WORDTAG O radical
57 WORDTAG O trade
12 WORDTAG O significant
37 WORDTAG O Foreign
26 WORDTAG O buy
7 WORDTAG O Third
6 WORDTAG O dated
164 WORDTAG O no
10 WORDTAG O customers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Villeneuve
5 WORDTAG I-LOC JOSE
15 WORDTAG O pact
8 WORDTAG O mandate
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vaduz
11 WORDTAG O protection
6 WORDTAG O .538
14 WORDTAG O snapped
9 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANCISCO
51 WORDTAG O drawn
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SV
15 WORDTAG O futures
32 WORDTAG O free
6 WORDTAG O consensus
6 WORDTAG O faster
8 WORDTAG O casualties
6 WORDTAG O split
11 WORDTAG O faction
18 WORDTAG O 80
8 WORDTAG O LEADING
5 WORDTAG O Premier
37 WORDTAG O died
125 WORDTAG O only
28 WORDTAG O unless
5 WORDTAG O allied
11 WORDTAG O tough
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Suwon
11 WORDTAG O doctors
8 WORDTAG I-PER Maleeva
10 WORDTAG O drive
62 WORDTAG O war
13 WORDTAG O helped
22 WORDTAG O killing
259 WORDTAG O 7
48 WORDTAG O already
6 WORDTAG O ....
14 WORDTAG O almost
42 WORDTAG O countries
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Army
5 WORDTAG O walkover
8 WORDTAG I-PER Smith
27 WORDTAG O L
36 WORDTAG O conference
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kimiko
11 WORDTAG O prevent
23 WORDTAG O decided
51 WORDTAG O another
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Twins
20 WORDTAG O couple
11 WORDTAG O Our
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
7 WORDTAG O 40,000
19 WORDTAG O analyst
6 WORDTAG O MON
5 WORDTAG O Commander
5 WORDTAG O deny
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Spanish
5 WORDTAG O investigations
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ivanisevic
8 WORDTAG O repeatedly
14 WORDTAG I-PER Muster
19 WORDTAG O remained
51 WORDTAG I-PER Paul
12 WORDTAG I-PER Washington
5 WORDTAG O .527
7 WORDTAG O hunt
18 WORDTAG I-PER Christie
36 WORDTAG O tour
6 WORDTAG O 1987
36 WORDTAG O does
24 WORDTAG I-ORG London
5 WORDTAG O films
6 WORDTAG O signal
23 WORDTAG O armed
28 WORDTAG O rise
155 WORDTAG O But
34 WORDTAG O order
15 WORDTAG I-ORG HOUSTON
6 WORDTAG O seat
6 WORDTAG O expects
5 WORDTAG O Health
19 WORDTAG O ball
91 WORDTAG O matches
12 WORDTAG I-PER Seles
8 WORDTAG I-ORG PLO
120 WORDTAG O match
28 WORDTAG O soon
5 WORDTAG I-PER Foe
25 WORDTAG O prefix
36 WORDTAG O March
8 WORDTAG O lift
85 WORDTAG O 71
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SYDNEY
26 WORDTAG O completed
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
8 WORDTAG O landing
15 WORDTAG O fight
9 WORDTAG O 25,000
30 WORDTAG O call
16 WORDTAG O walked
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Milan
14 WORDTAG O though
7 WORDTAG O Earlier
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Blacks
5 WORDTAG O association
55 WORDTAG I-MISC American
7 WORDTAG I-LOC CAIRO
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Algerian
1784 WORDTAG I-LOC _INITCAP_
74 WORDTAG O 7-6
14 WORDTAG O guerrilla
14 WORDTAG O suspected
8 WORDTAG O medal
11 WORDTAG O 15-11
5 WORDTAG I-ORG GPG
9 WORDTAG O SUMMARY
25 WORDTAG I-ORG PUK
7 WORDTAG I-MISC GRAND
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Hungary
5 WORDTAG O remarkable
9 WORDTAG O People
12 WORDTAG I-PER Rose
6 WORDTAG I-PER Batistuta
43 WORDTAG O agreement
9 WORDTAG O Did
7 WORDTAG O troubled
6 WORDTAG O 108
21 WORDTAG O copper
48 WORDTAG O IN
8 WORDTAG I-ORG BOJ
15 WORDTAG I-ORG San
19 WORDTAG O risk
5 WORDTAG I-PER Shane
144 WORDTAG O time
5 WORDTAG O TUESDAY
36 WORDTAG O ceasefire
25 WORDTAG I-PER Netanyahu
10 WORDTAG O why
6 WORDTAG O bids
29 WORDTAG O An
6 WORDTAG O size
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Centre
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesex
12 WORDTAG O show
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Treasury
13 WORDTAG O issued
5 WORDTAG O crown
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Sox
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Saudi
147 WORDTAG O week
9 WORDTAG O nearby
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Eindhoven
19 WORDTAG O Division
17 WORDTAG I-PER van
9 WORDTAG O holding
104 WORDTAG I-ORG of
143 WORDTAG O could
91 WORDTAG O 69
27 WORDTAG O border
280 WORDTAG O million
5 WORDTAG O 5.5
16 WORDTAG O water
6 WORDTAG O highly
10 WORDTAG O hurt
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Wellman
25 WORDTAG O FOR
12 WORDTAG I-ORG PKK
34 WORDTAG I-PER Thomas
5 WORDTAG O fined
98 WORDTAG O back
57 WORDTAG O cents
25 WORDTAG O ground
28 WORDTAG O see
7 WORDTAG I-PER El
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lynch
53 WORDTAG O 74
102 WORDTAG I-MISC _RARE_
8 WORDTAG O 325
25 WORDTAG O tie
36 WORDTAG O might
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Central
5 WORDTAG O word
15 WORDTAG I-ORG OAKLAND
13 WORDTAG O accident
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Brisbane
6 WORDTAG O publicly
8 WORDTAG O baht
6 WORDTAG O easy
8 WORDTAG O SCOREBOARD
86 WORDTAG O being
19 WORDTAG O bought
38 WORDTAG O attack
7 WORDTAG O launch
20 WORDTAG O costs
6 WORDTAG I-PER Lawrie
12 WORDTAG I-ORG RTRS
7 WORDTAG O equaliser
42 WORDTAG O away
95 WORDTAG O president
10 WORDTAG O quarter-finals
7 WORDTAG O 11.
5 WORDTAG O fewer
10 WORDTAG O research
30 WORDTAG O details
5 WORDTAG O 599
48 WORDTAG O many
8 WORDTAG O aged
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damon
8 WORDTAG O infusion
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nicolas
5 WORDTAG O Sir
5 WORDTAG O Financial
5 WORDTAG O substantial
5 WORDTAG O .466
6 WORDTAG O DATE
9 WORDTAG O doubles
22 WORDTAG O protest
6 WORDTAG I-PER Phil
6 WORDTAG O widespread
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
5 WORDTAG O instructions
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Marseille
5 WORDTAG I-LOC N.J.
7 WORDTAG O stabbed
9 WORDTAG I-PER Reagan
132 WORDTAG O SOCCER
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
6 WORDTAG O dn
14 WORDTAG O announcement
15 WORDTAG O rugby
102 WORDTAG O 14
8 WORDTAG O talking
6 WORDTAG O Income
17 WORDTAG I-ORG ST
13 WORDTAG I-PER Moin
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Minnesota
11 WORDTAG O send
6 WORDTAG O Summaries
8 WORDTAG O observers
9 WORDTAG I-PER Fred
11 WORDTAG I-PER Arantxa
5 WORDTAG O paint
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Microsoft
13 WORDTAG I-PER Marc
15 WORDTAG O property
5 WORDTAG O unclear
5 WORDTAG I-LOC CARLSBAD
34 WORDTAG O members
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Louis
7 WORDTAG O warrants
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
13 WORDTAG O injuries
14 WORDTAG O crew
9 WORDTAG O shown
9 WORDTAG O failure
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
7 WORDTAG O balls
8 WORDTAG I-PER Svetlana
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malaysia
8 WORDTAG I-LOC de
13 WORDTAG I-PER Lauck
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Tour
110 WORDTAG I-LOC Spain
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Games
2036 WORDTAG O on
6 WORDTAG O families
10 WORDTAG O additional
5 WORDTAG O Asked
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Davis
49 WORDTAG I-MISC GMT
8 WORDTAG O became
22 WORDTAG O drug
57 WORDTAG O 60
19 WORDTAG I-LOC WASHINGTON
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Amsterdam
25 WORDTAG I-PER _RARE_
9 WORDTAG O 1998
6 WORDTAG O ferry
7 WORDTAG O internal
47 WORDTAG O following
14 WORDTAG O Secretary
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Swedish
5 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANKFURT
12 WORDTAG O session
6 WORDTAG I-PER Takemura
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Arabs
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tom
7 WORDTAG I-PER Baker
23 WORDTAG O similar
6 WORDTAG O legislature
5 WORDTAG I-PER Silva
25 WORDTAG O 58
9 WORDTAG O Their
7 WORDTAG I-MISC A
2178 WORDTAG O "
18 WORDTAG O probably
25 WORDTAG O rebel
5 WORDTAG O blown
14 WORDTAG I-LOC HONG
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vienna
106 WORDTAG O do
5 WORDTAG O laws
5 WORDTAG O aims
41 WORDTAG O index
11 WORDTAG O retired
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Best
5 WORDTAG O tell
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamas
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mozambique
8 WORDTAG O 86
10 WORDTAG I-PER Tendulkar
6 WORDTAG O 15-7
6 WORDTAG O yards
28 WORDTAG O how
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Thailand
10 WORDTAG O clash
5 WORDTAG O aboard
13 WORDTAG O fired
5 WORDTAG O sexually
25 WORDTAG O problem
8 WORDTAG I-PER Knight
303 WORDTAG O percent
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Aires
10 WORDTAG O WINS
5 WORDTAG O bottle
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hingis
59 WORDTAG O both
9 WORDTAG O stable
12 WORDTAG O leadership
6 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S
6 WORDTAG I-PER Brad
29 WORDTAG O got
7 WORDTAG O assessment
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Colombian
25 WORDTAG O here
8 WORDTAG O 280
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kaluwitharana
11 WORDTAG I-PER Wilson
5 WORDTAG O otherwise
23 WORDTAG O land
7 WORDTAG I-PER Judith
11 WORDTAG O barley
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Charity
10 WORDTAG O barrels
9 WORDTAG I-ORG White
5 WORDTAG O window
14 WORDTAG O homes
6 WORDTAG O limit
5 WORDTAG O promoted
14 WORDTAG O V
14 WORDTAG O white
5 WORDTAG O representing
35 WORDTAG O us
10 WORDTAG O quite
21 WORDTAG O cricket
30 WORDTAG I-LOC _RARE_
5 WORDTAG O suits
7 WORDTAG I-PER Yoshikawa
18 WORDTAG O commission
5 WORDTAG O decisive
5 WORDTAG O venue
6 WORDTAG O beyond
6 WORDTAG O units
6 WORDTAG O 1,500
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eddie
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Frankfurt
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Election
9 WORDTAG I-PER Roger
9 WORDTAG O midnight
8 WORDTAG O route
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
84 WORDTAG O peace
5 WORDTAG I-PER V.
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linhart
6 WORDTAG O respect
12 WORDTAG O gun
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johansson
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Lebanon
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Colorado
5 WORDTAG O unseeded
8 WORDTAG O apparently
10 WORDTAG O suffering
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Old
7 WORDTAG O flown
12 WORDTAG O dismissed
7 WORDTAG O 8.0
8 WORDTAG O difficulties
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MADRID
20 WORDTAG O name
16 WORDTAG O forward
8 WORDTAG O Over
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kandahar
8 WORDTAG O Thousands
5 WORDTAG O negotiator
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
29 WORDTAG O named
9 WORDTAG O replace
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jimmy
7 WORDTAG O 4,000
9 WORDTAG O earned
7 WORDTAG O hog
19 WORDTAG O 47
6 WORDTAG O hat-trick
18 WORDTAG O believe
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Durham
5 WORDTAG O TV
5 WORDTAG O cannabis
155 WORDTAG O Sunday
5 WORDTAG O Among
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc.
5 WORDTAG O referendum
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Calif.
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BEIJING
15 WORDTAG I-MISC War
5 WORDTAG O taxi
12 WORDTAG O quickly
5 WORDTAG O parent
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Park
154 WORDTAG O more
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Daily
6 WORDTAG O athletes
6 WORDTAG I-PER Basuki
5 WORDTAG O demands
6 WORDTAG O wages
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Iran
16 WORDTAG O seventh
26 WORDTAG O Total
5 WORDTAG O missionary
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Werder
6 WORDTAG I-PER Marcus
56 WORDTAG O gave
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hatoyama
13 WORDTAG O purchase
36 WORDTAG O 're
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Stirling
7 WORDTAG O successive
8 WORDTAG O concerned
142 WORDTAG I-LOC Germany
14 WORDTAG O data
8 WORDTAG I-PER Charles
5 WORDTAG O highlights
8 WORDTAG O threat
10 WORDTAG O peso
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Port
5 WORDTAG O violation
9 WORDTAG O stepped
8 WORDTAG O definitely
7 WORDTAG O check
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Sarajevo
11 WORDTAG O however
8 WORDTAG O ceremony
5 WORDTAG I-PER Elena
46 WORDTAG I-LOC West
8 WORDTAG O acquisition
78 WORDTAG O around
11 WORDTAG O mother
6 WORDTAG O equivalent
25 WORDTAG I-PER Bill
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
6 WORDTAG I-MISC 96
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
30 WORDTAG I-ORG CHICAGO
10 WORDTAG O three-run
20 WORDTAG O His
21 WORDTAG I-PER Richard
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rovers
6 WORDTAG O Chg
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ipswich
8 WORDTAG O gets
6 WORDTAG O worldwide
388 WORDTAG O first
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Desk
22 WORDTAG O bomb
5 WORDTAG O crackdown
6 WORDTAG O unfortunate
15 WORDTAG I-ORG State
45 WORDTAG O 31
6 WORDTAG O impossible
12 WORDTAG O involving
39 WORDTAG O 40
7 WORDTAG O theft
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tim
6 WORDTAG O G
10 WORDTAG O relief
5 WORDTAG O importance
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hong
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Rome
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesbrough
30 WORDTAG O law
25 WORDTAG I-ORG Exchange
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mohammad
5 WORDTAG O blocked
40 WORDTAG O business
5 WORDTAG O meets
306 WORDTAG O they
6 WORDTAG O livestock
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ANGELES
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Windows
109 WORDTAG O President
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Johannesburg
19 WORDTAG O orders
28 WORDTAG I-PER Mushtaq
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Journal
16 WORDTAG O family
7 WORDTAG O mean
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bernd
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
14 WORDTAG O auction
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sharif
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Virginia
7 WORDTAG O river
15 WORDTAG I-PER Diana
8 WORDTAG O shows
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anderson
37 WORDTAG O led
7 WORDTAG O sterling
5 WORDTAG O quick
14 WORDTAG I-LOC COLOMBO
26 WORDTAG O 53
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TORONTO
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mikael
5 WORDTAG O northwest
5 WORDTAG I-PER Adams
10 WORDTAG O Deputy
5 WORDTAG O buyers
15 WORDTAG O delayed
12 WORDTAG O scoring
17 WORDTAG I-PER J.
36 WORDTAG I-LOC Ireland
6 WORDTAG O minimum
14 WORDTAG O CYCLING
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sun
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Ducati
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pinas
8 WORDTAG O veterinary
36 WORDTAG O case
111 WORDTAG O him
23 WORDTAG O 52
40 WORDTAG O c
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Argentine
10 WORDTAG O beef
9 WORDTAG O preparing
8 WORDTAG I-PER Slight
20 WORDTAG O products
37 WORDTAG O best
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Data
7 WORDTAG O versus
11 WORDTAG O fast
7 WORDTAG O partners
8 WORDTAG I-PER Ali
30 WORDTAG O squad
14 WORDTAG O shortly
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Union
12 WORDTAG O welfare
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bedie
5 WORDTAG I-PER Flower
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kingdom
11 WORDTAG O lei
15 WORDTAG O commander
48 WORDTAG O including
15 WORDTAG O either
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bureau
39 WORDTAG O area
10 WORDTAG I-PER Johan
5 WORDTAG O winds
75 WORDTAG O number
8 WORDTAG O Sale
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Benetton
6 WORDTAG O heads
16 WORDTAG I-PER C.
7 WORDTAG O ca
5 WORDTAG I-PER Aki
25 WORDTAG O conditions
45 WORDTAG O work
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wolverhampton
20 WORDTAG O find
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Ohio
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Reef
13 WORDTAG O bourse
12 WORDTAG I-PER Huber
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tyrrell
13 WORDTAG O buying
7 WORDTAG O copies
19 WORDTAG O release
9 WORDTAG O politicians
8 WORDTAG O fever
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Dm
43 WORDTAG O plans
37 WORDTAG O without
5 WORDTAG O pills
6 WORDTAG I-ORG India
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Ssangbangwool
27 WORDTAG I-LOC East
12 WORDTAG I-MISC 95
581 WORDTAG O 4
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Leeds
25 WORDTAG O wife
119 WORDTAG O 13
6 WORDTAG O Dec
6 WORDTAG O 212-859-1650
5 WORDTAG O crossing
6 WORDTAG O 15-9
120 WORDTAG O off
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Odra
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Wimbledon
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
83 WORDTAG O talks
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Mideast
5 WORDTAG I-ORG TV
13 WORDTAG O And
15 WORDTAG O kidnapped
72 WORDTAG O foreign
7 WORDTAG O hot
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erbakan
12 WORDTAG O democracy
15 WORDTAG O RESULT
10 WORDTAG O danger
6 WORDTAG O estimate
7 WORDTAG O organisations
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lance
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Honda
7 WORDTAG I-PER Sergi
16 WORDTAG O cooperation
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Angolan
35 WORDTAG O average
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Belgian
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Philadelphia
9 WORDTAG O knew
9 WORDTAG O jump
5 WORDTAG O pulp
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Khartoum
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
14 WORDTAG O tight
12 WORDTAG I-ORG USDA
11 WORDTAG O attend
15 WORDTAG I-PER S.
14 WORDTAG O students
14 WORDTAG O qualifying
15 WORDTAG O administration
59 WORDTAG O town
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ballybunion
5 WORDTAG I-MISC post-Soviet
6 WORDTAG O secure
8 WORDTAG I-PER Julie
7 WORDTAG O failing
6 WORDTAG O slaughter
8 WORDTAG O construction
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Haj
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Jordanian
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslems
5 WORDTAG O five-run
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Commodities
10 WORDTAG O sprint
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Patriotic
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alain
13 WORDTAG O stages
12 WORDTAG O 79
13 WORDTAG O gross
32 WORDTAG I-LOC Bank
19 WORDTAG O charge
197 WORDTAG O 10
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kenny
15 WORDTAG O protests
14 WORDTAG O SCORES
57 WORDTAG O make
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Russians
22 WORDTAG O premier
19 WORDTAG O governor
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rosati
5 WORDTAG O escaped
6 WORDTAG O safety
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Assembly
29 WORDTAG O process
10 WORDTAG O proposal
15 WORDTAG O light
8 WORDTAG O Gov
5 WORDTAG O attributable
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Bundesliga
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Queens
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Norwegian
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazprom
22 WORDTAG I-PER Alex
5 WORDTAG O titles
11 WORDTAG O determine
10 WORDTAG O OUT
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
7 WORDTAG O abuses
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Belarus
15 WORDTAG O consumer
5 WORDTAG I-PER Oliver
19 WORDTAG O competition
6 WORDTAG O believes
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Bucharest
5 WORDTAG I-PER Specter
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Trent
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Gulf
10 WORDTAG O scattered
14 WORDTAG O factions
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Americans
9 WORDTAG O custody
16 WORDTAG O passenger
5 WORDTAG I-PER Larry
7 WORDTAG O THURSDAY
5 WORDTAG O walking
14 WORDTAG O seeking
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MONTREAL
63 WORDTAG O 1995
25 WORDTAG O parties
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Czech
61 WORDTAG O close
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlanta
5 WORDTAG O producers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Guzman
19 WORDTAG O sign
5 WORDTAG O CONFIRMED
3382 WORDTAG O to
26 WORDTAG I-LOC AMSTERDAM
7 WORDTAG O continuing
5 WORDTAG O larger
6 WORDTAG O dissidents
5 WORDTAG O pending
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Zealand
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Texas
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Zaire
53 WORDTAG O agreed
13 WORDTAG I-LOC MANCHESTER
10 WORDTAG O B
13 WORDTAG O AFTER
7 WORDTAG O fallen
9 WORDTAG O capped
356 WORDTAG O --
9 WORDTAG O permission
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jorge
8 WORDTAG O 30,000
5 WORDTAG O From
5 WORDTAG O load
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LANKA
7 WORDTAG O affected
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dean
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wednesday
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rangarajan
10 WORDTAG O Officials
16 WORDTAG O voters
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mary
7 WORDTAG O Jan
13 WORDTAG O begin
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
13 WORDTAG O weaker
26 WORDTAG O gold
11 WORDTAG O Revenue
39 WORDTAG O Standings
11 WORDTAG O warned
10 WORDTAG O guilty
17 WORDTAG O drove
27 WORDTAG O road
5 WORDTAG O 11.00
6 WORDTAG O scientist
16 WORDTAG O job
12 WORDTAG O offices
8 WORDTAG O hijacking
6 WORDTAG O operator
8 WORDTAG I-LOC HOUSTON
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
7 WORDTAG O customer
5 WORDTAG I-PER Prince
10 WORDTAG O witnesses
24 WORDTAG O treaty
35 WORDTAG O overs
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Larnaca
9 WORDTAG O captured
74 WORDTAG O days
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
6 WORDTAG O placings
9 WORDTAG O together
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Cyprus
46 WORDTAG O forces
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Boston
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
14 WORDTAG O walk
8 WORDTAG O gathering
7 WORDTAG O stance
5 WORDTAG O trafficking
43 WORDTAG O This
11 WORDTAG O premium
5 WORDTAG O div
33 WORDTAG O rose
41 WORDTAG O main
21 WORDTAG O stocks
7 WORDTAG O backed
35 WORDTAG O prime
10 WORDTAG O row
5 WORDTAG O Only
9 WORDTAG O expectations
22 WORDTAG O important
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
11 WORDTAG O surplus
12 WORDTAG O income
5 WORDTAG O penalties
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
16 WORDTAG O losses
6 WORDTAG O reply
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hansa
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Soviet
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Leverkusen
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mapei
15 WORDTAG I-LOC CITY
12 WORDTAG O resume
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Europe
10 WORDTAG O serve
10 WORDTAG O sentenced
14 WORDTAG O ON
23 WORDTAG O offer
7 WORDTAG I-PER Walker
13 WORDTAG O hands
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Ford
7 WORDTAG O exact
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Day
8 WORDTAG O remove
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jeff
5 WORDTAG O 12th
5 WORDTAG O weakening
9 WORDTAG O allegedly
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Fiorentina
80 WORDTAG O take
36 WORDTAG O little
5 WORDTAG O shift
5 WORDTAG O appearance
5 WORDTAG O Five
6 WORDTAG I-PER Karina
8 WORDTAG I-ORG 1860
10 WORDTAG O committed
8 WORDTAG O SQUAD
5 WORDTAG O quake
13 WORDTAG O claimed
9 WORDTAG O lose
127 WORDTAG O company
15 WORDTAG O currently
13 WORDTAG O accept
8 WORDTAG O rallied
8 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neal
5 WORDTAG O owners
7 WORDTAG O privatization
34 WORDTAG O service
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Group
12 WORDTAG O barter
6 WORDTAG O dealing
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vatican
557 WORDTAG O has
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ieng
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Home
27 WORDTAG O making
21 WORDTAG I-ORG Security
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Sri
13 WORDTAG I-MISC FRENCH
8 WORDTAG O margins
12 WORDTAG I-PER Maria
5 WORDTAG O YEAR-AGO
27 WORDTAG O straight
14 WORDTAG O rally
5 WORDTAG O acquire
31 WORDTAG O guerrillas
507 WORDTAG O an
37 WORDTAG O club
7 WORDTAG O holders
7 WORDTAG I-PER McGrath
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
12 WORDTAG O boost
23 WORDTAG O trial
17 WORDTAG O concern
5 WORDTAG O eye
17 WORDTAG O although
12 WORDTAG O front
6 WORDTAG O Despite
10 WORDTAG O announce
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
13 WORDTAG O entering
306 WORDTAG O its
6 WORDTAG O relay
21 WORDTAG O black
8 WORDTAG O handling
20 WORDTAG I-PER N.
6 WORDTAG O manufacturers
14 WORDTAG O different
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Service
9 WORDTAG O present
8 WORDTAG I-PER Fernando
21 WORDTAG O sector
5 WORDTAG I-LOC UAE
40 WORDTAG O army
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Puchon
13 WORDTAG O address
10 WORDTAG O create
7 WORDTAG O X
10 WORDTAG O apartheid
5 WORDTAG O skilled
16 WORDTAG I-MISC MAJOR
34 WORDTAG O across
26 WORDTAG O nuclear
30 WORDTAG O yen
6 WORDTAG O editorial
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
10 WORDTAG O 4.0
9 WORDTAG O largely
11 WORDTAG O 7-2
20 WORDTAG O steady
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Palace
9 WORDTAG O researchers
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Stuttgart
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Tibet
9 WORDTAG I-ORG County
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Gaza
19 WORDTAG I-PER Chris
11 WORDTAG I-ORG )
8 WORDTAG O ousted
122 WORDTAG O there
11 WORDTAG O gained
8 WORDTAG O keeping
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Guingamp
9 WORDTAG O values
5 WORDTAG O MPs
9 WORDTAG O addition
85 WORDTAG O added
71 WORDTAG O 100
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Sao
43 WORDTAG O share
7 WORDTAG I-LOC KANSAS
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahamas
37 WORDTAG O available
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Rostock
63 WORDTAG O 7-5
26 WORDTAG I-PER Mullally
17 WORDTAG I-PER Van
10 WORDTAG I-PER Bailey
13 WORDTAG I-PER Gary
6 WORDTAG O drought
98 WORDTAG O shares
5 WORDTAG O defenders
10 WORDTAG O 3,000
7 WORDTAG I-PER Brooke
14 WORDTAG O GAMES
34 WORDTAG O October
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Hungarian
12 WORDTAG O afternoon
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
7 WORDTAG O 16.
13 WORDTAG O west
5 WORDTAG O 59th
7 WORDTAG O embargo
12 WORDTAG O millions
602 WORDTAG O as
6 WORDTAG O alone
6 WORDTAG I-MISC serie
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Polish
17 WORDTAG O investment
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Alaska
24 WORDTAG O denotes
9 WORDTAG O success
7 WORDTAG O grenades
13 WORDTAG O 11th
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kucera
16873 WORDTAG O _RARE_
5 WORDTAG O badly
9 WORDTAG O H1
88 WORDTAG I-LOC Russia
16 WORDTAG O accuracy
6 WORDTAG I-PER Michelle
9 WORDTAG I-LOC of
8 WORDTAG O unc
5 WORDTAG O iron
28 WORDTAG O believed
5 WORDTAG O 60th
14 WORDTAG O 6-7
7 WORDTAG O true
5 WORDTAG O riyal
53 WORDTAG O until
6 WORDTAG O amid
8 WORDTAG O CAPS
31 WORDTAG O 2-0
7 WORDTAG O hear
8 WORDTAG O CHAMPIONSHIP
23 WORDTAG O investors
5 WORDTAG O Nearly
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Massachusetts
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbian
6 WORDTAG O 1986
9 WORDTAG O boxes
5 WORDTAG O ACTUAL
39 WORDTAG O growth
66 WORDTAG O 66
9 WORDTAG I-PER Tillstrom
7 WORDTAG I-PER Date
5 WORDTAG I-PER Amanda
13 WORDTAG O responsible
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Preston
59 WORDTAG O lower
6 WORDTAG O pushed
5 WORDTAG O set-top
12 WORDTAG O rather
8 WORDTAG O century
6 WORDTAG O pitched
5 WORDTAG O dozens
69 WORDTAG O 50
22 WORDTAG I-PER D.
13 WORDTAG O investigators
18 WORDTAG O range
7 WORDTAG O kidnapping
45 WORDTAG O way
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aslan
64 WORDTAG O 67
5 WORDTAG O wing
8 WORDTAG O organised
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Karlsruhe
11 WORDTAG O material
126 WORDTAG O Saturday
6 WORDTAG O attempted
7 WORDTAG O venture
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Singapore
19 WORDTAG I-MISC ENGLISH
8 WORDTAG I-ORG GKS
11 WORDTAG O advantage
5 WORDTAG O KV
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Phillies
561 WORDTAG O had
6 WORDTAG O highest
36 WORDTAG O sent
14 WORDTAG I-MISC DUTCH
6 WORDTAG O dragged
5 WORDTAG O planes
16 WORDTAG O Extras
22 WORDTAG O AUGUST
11 WORDTAG I-PER Tony
343 WORDTAG O 6
5 WORDTAG O 100,000
17 WORDTAG O resignation
5 WORDTAG O metal
5 WORDTAG I-PER Broadhurst
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Namibia
22 WORDTAG O tabulated
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grobbelaar
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Libya
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Street
13 WORDTAG I-MISC RBI
8 WORDTAG O finance
7 WORDTAG O 521-8
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wells
7 WORDTAG I-PER Kabariti
19 WORDTAG O farmers
5 WORDTAG O partly
362 WORDTAG O $
13 WORDTAG O TEST
16 WORDTAG O scores
6 WORDTAG I-ORG PUNR
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Portsmouth
29 WORDTAG O daily
10 WORDTAG O leads
14 WORDTAG O product
7 WORDTAG I-PER Billy
59 WORDTAG O eight
8 WORDTAG I-PER Marco
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Wheat
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Yugoslav
16 WORDTAG O positions
11 WORDTAG I-PER Fox
9 WORDTAG O comes
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Kawasaki
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
17 WORDTAG O among
23 WORDTAG O Scorers
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Colchester
75 WORDTAG O 68
9 WORDTAG O enter
5 WORDTAG O soybeans
181 WORDTAG O Friday
15 WORDTAG O owned
5 WORDTAG O demonstrators
5 WORDTAG O shr
80 WORDTAG O held
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ATLANTA
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Championship
7 WORDTAG O sentence
8 WORDTAG I-ORG in
6 WORDTAG O developed
11 WORDTAG O estimates
7 WORDTAG I-ORG ACC
31 WORDTAG O fifth
16 WORDTAG I-PER Martinez
40 WORDTAG O scored
92 WORDTAG O while
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Nicaragua
8 WORDTAG O station
43 WORDTAG O test
5 WORDTAG O usual
10 WORDTAG O Note
5 WORDTAG I-PER Naoko
12 WORDTAG O strategic
33 WORDTAG O bonds
29 WORDTAG I-LOC CHICAGO
7 WORDTAG O deposit
7 WORDTAG O tied
30 WORDTAG O That
8 WORDTAG O shut
7 WORDTAG I-PER Liam
12 WORDTAG O direct
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Human
7 WORDTAG I-ORG TVM
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Itar-Tass
46 WORDTAG O authorities
14 WORDTAG O grand
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Angeles
5 WORDTAG O engine
14 WORDTAG I-ORG FLORIDA
5 WORDTAG O youth
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
20 WORDTAG O votes
15 WORDTAG O houses
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Calcutta
17 WORDTAG I-LOC MOSCOW
19 WORDTAG O 4-6
20 WORDTAG O dropped
52 WORDTAG I-MISC Australian
5 WORDTAG O insistence
34 WORDTAG O airport
7 WORDTAG O certainly
16 WORDTAG O recently
5 WORDTAG O Gluten
36 WORDTAG O ban
27 WORDTAG O levels
15 WORDTAG O avoid
5 WORDTAG I-PER Arnold
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tankan
5 WORDTAG O cast
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
58 WORDTAG O deal
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Lankan
40 WORDTAG O rights
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gold
10 WORDTAG O reason
8 WORDTAG O 12.0
16 WORDTAG I-PER Graf
7 WORDTAG I-ORG CNIEC
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Togo
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Queen
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Celsius
23 WORDTAG O need
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damm
5 WORDTAG O Pro
17 WORDTAG O output
133 WORDTAG O since
285 WORDTAG O Thursday
5 WORDTAG I-MISC McLaren
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Brussels
8 WORDTAG O elected
5 WORDTAG O diverted
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrix
330 WORDTAG O would
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jack
21 WORDTAG O federal
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Index
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
5 WORDTAG O particularly
6 WORDTAG O rice
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Notts
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Arch
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ken
5 WORDTAG O setting
5 WORDTAG O Opposition
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazeta
28 WORDTAG O halftime
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joyce
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costantino
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbertson
56 WORDTAG O pct
5 WORDTAG O FRIENDLY
6 WORDTAG O 26th
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Agency
9 WORDTAG I-PER Brunswijk
23 WORDTAG O complete
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weaver
71 WORDTAG O political
5 WORDTAG O painful
33 WORDTAG O Two
291 WORDTAG O out
12 WORDTAG O King
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Island
19 WORDTAG I-MISC A$
20 WORDTAG O tonne
5 WORDTAG O telling
5 WORDTAG O merely
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arminia
11 WORDTAG O ever
17 WORDTAG O polls
7 WORDTAG O 12.
78 WORDTAG O should
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Helens
5 WORDTAG O glass
74 WORDTAG O b
107 WORDTAG O third
5 WORDTAG O 1999
14 WORDTAG O secret
9 WORDTAG O rail
17 WORDTAG O rules
10 WORDTAG O threw
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pollock
41 WORDTAG O north
45 WORDTAG O troops
8 WORDTAG I-PER Kelly
11 WORDTAG O neighbouring
117 WORDTAG O down
16 WORDTAG I-LOC BRUSSELS
7 WORDTAG O festival
36 WORDTAG O right
21 WORDTAG O eastern
6 WORDTAG O medallist
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Portuguese
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Medicare
1004 WORDTAG I-MISC _INITCAP_
582 WORDTAG O he
16 WORDTAG O running
9 WORDTAG O rating
11 WORDTAG I-ORG IVAC
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Vienna
6 WORDTAG O 32.0
50 WORDTAG O my
10 WORDTAG I-PER Andrew
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Scottish
50 WORDTAG O place
8 WORDTAG O merger
8 WORDTAG O none
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Barrick
5 WORDTAG O ordering
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Khmer
7 WORDTAG O attempts
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Amoco
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Labour
10 WORDTAG O WITH
66 WORDTAG O left
8 WORDTAG O striking
8 WORDTAG I-PER Miguel
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Glamorgan
24 WORDTAG O PRESS
5615 WORDTAG I-PER _INITCAP_
30 WORDTAG O train
5 WORDTAG O football
71 WORDTAG O per
134 WORDTAG O years
22 WORDTAG I-ORG &
24 WORDTAG O himself
34 WORDTAG O planned
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rabbani
8 WORDTAG O room
9 WORDTAG O closing
8 WORDTAG O unknown
7 WORDTAG O hopes
11 WORDTAG O 4-0
12 WORDTAG O passed
6 WORDTAG O monitoring
12 WORDTAG O grain
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferrari
5 WORDTAG O endorse
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Warburg
12 WORDTAG O progress
5 WORDTAG O Data
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hashimoto
14 WORDTAG O body
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Karachi
7 WORDTAG O facing
13 WORDTAG O crowd
6 WORDTAG I-PER Tommi
5 WORDTAG O freedom
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Reading
29 WORDTAG O result
8 WORDTAG I-ORG MDS
17 WORDTAG O operation
6 WORDTAG O Maybe
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Rio
6 WORDTAG O toward
18 WORDTAG O officers
10 WORDTAG O five-year
5 WORDTAG O bush
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CANADIAN
121 WORDTAG O 1996
6 WORDTAG O kuna
6 WORDTAG O love
10 WORDTAG O built
5 WORDTAG O handgun
8 WORDTAG O 160
61 WORDTAG O newsroom
9 WORDTAG O disappointing
5 WORDTAG O boss
6 WORDTAG O compatriot
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ligier
15 WORDTAG O figure
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Star
8 WORDTAG O backing
5 WORDTAG O realised
18 WORDTAG O diplomat
5 WORDTAG O sport
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Queensland
60 WORDTAG O man
8 WORDTAG O schedule
38 WORDTAG O accused
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
531 WORDTAG O were
12 WORDTAG I-MISC '
5 WORDTAG O intensive
21 WORDTAG O air
14 WORDTAG O 5-7
6 WORDTAG O contribute
34 WORDTAG O stories
5 WORDTAG O sexual
5 WORDTAG O stations
23 WORDTAG O 46
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nasdaq
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interpol
53 WORDTAG O dollar
9 WORDTAG O fellow
5 WORDTAG O contents
6 WORDTAG I-ORG IOC
16 WORDTAG O programme
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Grozny
9 WORDTAG O nomination
32 WORDTAG O interest
38 WORDTAG O strike
9 WORDTAG O supplies
61 WORDTAG I-LOC London
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
11 WORDTAG O continues
368 WORDTAG O been
6 WORDTAG O Finance
19 WORDTAG O December
40 WORDTAG O major
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Medical
8 WORDTAG O arrives
14 WORDTAG O emergency
7 WORDTAG O thin
20 WORDTAG O currency
7 WORDTAG O cup
5 WORDTAG O shed
18 WORDTAG O voting
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Oldham
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Lithuania
11 WORDTAG I-LOC BALTIMORE
5 WORDTAG O projects
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Canadian
2590 WORDTAG O _INITCAP_
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Salang
5 WORDTAG I-ORG PULPEX
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Treaty
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Pauli
389 WORDTAG O but
9 WORDTAG O served
9 WORDTAG O 1989
50 WORDTAG O CRICKET
9 WORDTAG O joint
5 WORDTAG O meal
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tehran
8 WORDTAG I-LOC COLORADO
5 WORDTAG O returning
5 WORDTAG O 12-year-old
9 WORDTAG O weak
9 WORDTAG O nor
7 WORDTAG O dark
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cairo
9 WORDTAG O detained
12 WORDTAG I-ORG California
11 WORDTAG O distribution
5 WORDTAG O aviation
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
8 WORDTAG O wrist
24 WORDTAG O 42
6 WORDTAG O 70th
37 WORDTAG O ministry
5 WORDTAG O 900
48 WORDTAG O OF
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NAC
6 WORDTAG O inventories
6 WORDTAG O shared
12 WORDTAG O stronger
9 WORDTAG I-PER Rios
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sandra
5 WORDTAG I-PER Healy
5 WORDTAG O garden
10 WORDTAG O carry
5 WORDTAG O searched
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Korea
7 WORDTAG O professional
10 WORDTAG I-PER Oncins
24 WORDTAG O winner
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Zastava
14 WORDTAG O approved
19 WORDTAG O 90
15 WORDTAG O 3-0
31 WORDTAG O term
14 WORDTAG O 2000
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tranmere
9 WORDTAG O consumers
58 WORDTAG O 72
20 WORDTAG O GB
16 WORDTAG O caused
14 WORDTAG I-ORG AG
9 WORDTAG I-PER Makinen
7 WORDTAG I-PER Koerts
12 WORDTAG O 212
19 WORDTAG O 'll
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Republican
6 WORDTAG O loaded
49 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli
32 WORDTAG I-PER A.
6 WORDTAG I-ORG AOL
7 WORDTAG O N
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Mexican
84 WORDTAG O At
24 WORDTAG O 300
7 WORDTAG O factors
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nestor
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackpool
8 WORDTAG O plays
25 WORDTAG O arrived
77 WORDTAG O elections
43 WORDTAG O national
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Kent
27 WORDTAG O scheduled
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Kremlin
7 WORDTAG O surprise
6 WORDTAG O cargoes
5 WORDTAG O riding
11 WORDTAG O speech
47 WORDTAG O 17
5 WORDTAG O exclusive
6 WORDTAG O slight
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Indonesia
21 WORDTAG I-MISC C$
8 WORDTAG O required
64 WORDTAG O vs.
18 WORDTAG O drew
7 WORDTAG I-PER Eriksson
8 WORDTAG O accord
7 WORDTAG O missed
5 WORDTAG O 2.6
10 WORDTAG O ties
17 WORDTAG I-ORG MINNESOTA
7 WORDTAG O humanitarian
46 WORDTAG I-ORG and
10 WORDTAG O 5,000
7 WORDTAG O fair
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Atlanta
14 WORDTAG O supply
5 WORDTAG O Nov
68 WORDTAG O country
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LOS
5 WORDTAG O recover
14 WORDTAG O launched
255 WORDTAG O Wednesday
7 WORDTAG O block
13 WORDTAG O industrial
6 WORDTAG O animals
6 WORDTAG O slam
29 WORDTAG O human
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Egypt
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Res
13 WORDTAG O debate
5 WORDTAG O selected
14 WORDTAG I-PER Alan
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Brazil
7 WORDTAG O anyone
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Duesseldorf
21 WORDTAG O defence
5 WORDTAG O 1980
65 WORDTAG O profit
12 WORDTAG O incident
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linford
5 WORDTAG O photographs
11 WORDTAG O 15-10
42 WORDTAG I-LOC Finland
5 WORDTAG I-MISC CLASSIC
5 WORDTAG O complex
8 WORDTAG O prosecutors
13 WORDTAG O target
7 WORDTAG O fuel
10 WORDTAG O pitch
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eales
5 WORDTAG O frost
5 WORDTAG I-PER Krajicek
5 WORDTAG O finds
12 WORDTAG O What
25 WORDTAG O full
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Fortuna
21 WORDTAG O drugs
11 WORDTAG O threatening
6 WORDTAG O midday
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
33 WORDTAG O declared
160 WORDTAG O into
15 WORDTAG O heavy
38 WORDTAG O winning
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Court
36 WORDTAG B-MISC _INITCAP_
45 WORDTAG O whether
49 WORDTAG I-MISC League
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Shanghai
6 WORDTAG O reach
6 WORDTAG O starter
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ivorian
11 WORDTAG I-MISC BSE
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sion
7 WORDTAG O controlled
29 WORDTAG O action
31 WORDTAG O hospital
56 WORDTAG O There
16 WORDTAG O Former
9 WORDTAG O let
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Munich
8 WORDTAG O slipped
18 WORDTAG O appeared
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Everton
7 WORDTAG O holes
10 WORDTAG O cancelled
14 WORDTAG O effect
9 WORDTAG O friend
7 WORDTAG I-PER Botham
5 WORDTAG O excellent
18 WORDTAG O jail
12 WORDTAG O 0-1
7 WORDTAG I-PER Roe
14 WORDTAG O act
53 WORDTAG O price
8 WORDTAG I-MISC EUROPEAN
9 WORDTAG O suicide
9 WORDTAG O trillion
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
5 WORDTAG O Trade
5 WORDTAG O spinal
8 WORDTAG O 85
19 WORDTAG O Sept
8 WORDTAG O struggle
124 WORDTAG I-LOC England
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovenia
6 WORDTAG O beating
28 WORDTAG O seeding
10 WORDTAG O headquarters
5 WORDTAG O giant
11 WORDTAG O reserve
5 WORDTAG O audience
5 WORDTAG O sending
9 WORDTAG O Group
8 WORDTAG O program
5 WORDTAG O detective
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tass
55 WORDTAG I-MISC European
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Athens
7 WORDTAG I-PER Woosnam
9 WORDTAG I-LOC WELLINGTON
167 WORDTAG O 1996-08-28
10 WORDTAG O existing
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Toyota
5 WORDTAG I-MISC SCOTTISH
42 WORDTAG O trading
49 WORDTAG O quoted
17 WORDTAG O farm
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magnus
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Beirut
26 WORDTAG O illegal
10 WORDTAG O fears
6 WORDTAG O 80th
120 WORDTAG O 11
12 WORDTAG I-PER Yasser
60 WORDTAG O say
23 WORDTAG O %
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympics
95 WORDTAG I-MISC Russian
6 WORDTAG O n.a
13 WORDTAG O ROUND
5 WORDTAG O RESEARCH
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Jerusalem
28 WORDTAG O 76
5 WORDTAG I-PER Heeswijk
5 WORDTAG O racing
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rohrabacher
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SRI
53 WORDTAG O 7.
18 WORDTAG O damage
13 WORDTAG O information
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ross
3690 WORDTAG I-ORG _INITCAP_
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Boston
12 WORDTAG I-LOC White
24 WORDTAG O goal
7 WORDTAG O fun
16 WORDTAG O 44
6 WORDTAG O Current
8 WORDTAG I-MISC OF
34 WORDTAG O Leading
30 WORDTAG O companies
21 WORDTAG O discuss
6 WORDTAG O abduction
10 WORDTAG I-PER Gajdos
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Damascus
7 WORDTAG O avoided
8 WORDTAG O answer
12 WORDTAG O sheep
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
5 WORDTAG O 600,000
14 WORDTAG O kph
7 WORDTAG O motor
10 WORDTAG O Dealers
19 WORDTAG O tender
5 WORDTAG O withdrew
5 WORDTAG O Close
5 WORDTAG O grew
6 WORDTAG O crop
7 WORDTAG O nations
49 WORDTAG I-PER Ahmed
7 WORDTAG O strikers
5 WORDTAG O Chief
15 WORDTAG O published
7 WORDTAG O +301
7 WORDTAG O .02
21 WORDTAG O injury
5 WORDTAG O pursue
5 WORDTAG I-PER Patricia
8 WORDTAG O reaching
7 WORDTAG O +1
6 WORDTAG O decline
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
163 WORDTAG O won
9 WORDTAG O storm
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mayfair
10 WORDTAG O New
23 WORDTAG O having
10 WORDTAG O Turnover
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nick
15 WORDTAG O towards
63 WORDTAG O very
26 WORDTAG O senior
5 WORDTAG I-ORG interior
5 WORDTAG O baby
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Nations
18 WORDTAG O evening
27 WORDTAG O 56
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bromwich
6 WORDTAG O motion
58 WORDTAG I-PER Mark
6 WORDTAG I-ORG America
9 WORDTAG O corporate
14 WORDTAG O aimed
7 WORDTAG O happen
26 WORDTAG O message
14 WORDTAG O threatened
19 WORDTAG O traffic
7275 WORDTAG O ,
30 WORDTAG O passengers
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
127 WORDTAG O state
7 WORDTAG O 12-15
11 WORDTAG O bottom
8 WORDTAG I-ORG SEC
5 WORDTAG O consulate
9 WORDTAG O commanding
7 WORDTAG O pledged
35 WORDTAG I-MISC Italian
16 WORDTAG O lap
8 WORDTAG I-PER Iliescu
6 WORDTAG O hoped
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Irish
44 WORDTAG O 18
97 WORDTAG O August
9 WORDTAG O throughout
7 WORDTAG I-PER Simpson
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Salomon
6 WORDTAG O governments
5 WORDTAG O Seven
5 WORDTAG O dictator
9 WORDTAG O D
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Angels
19 WORDTAG O sets
6 WORDTAG O corn
51 WORDTAG O refugees
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
9 WORDTAG O response
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Porto
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cocu
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gingrich
8 WORDTAG O 106
13 WORDTAG O blood
7 WORDTAG O brokers
5 WORDTAG O [
41 WORDTAG O money
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jon
9 WORDTAG O equal
22 WORDTAG O province
15 WORDTAG O remain
31 WORDTAG O forced
8 WORDTAG O capacity
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Yugoslavia
6 WORDTAG I-PER Conchita
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bistrita
9 WORDTAG O son
68 WORDTAG O seven
9 WORDTAG O Speaker
538 WORDTAG O his
8 WORDTAG O falling
28 WORDTAG I-PER Waqar
8 WORDTAG O initially
163 WORDTAG O we
26 WORDTAG O independence
7 WORDTAG O moving
149 WORDTAG O before
8 WORDTAG I-PER Sven
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Lens
7 WORDTAG O RALLYING
7 WORDTAG O abuse
6 WORDTAG O phase
15 WORDTAG O Fall
76 WORDTAG O party
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Emnid
8 WORDTAG O resign
92 WORDTAG O any
6 WORDTAG O 58th
137 WORDTAG O We
13 WORDTAG O broken
6 WORDTAG O Operating
6 WORDTAG O receive
31 WORDTAG O opening
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicestershire
13 WORDTAG O east
10 WORDTAG O brief
6 WORDTAG O quit
10 WORDTAG O investigation
5 WORDTAG O defends
137 WORDTAG O points
16 WORDTAG I-ORG KANSAS
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hassan
30 WORDTAG O despite
7 WORDTAG O activists
16 WORDTAG O admitted
16 WORDTAG I-PER Sampras
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Afghanistan
7 WORDTAG O moisture
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henman
11 WORDTAG I-PER Gough
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kubo
5 WORDTAG O negotiated
15 WORDTAG O starts
8 WORDTAG O Scoreboard
8 WORDTAG O Several
6 WORDTAG O resulted
12 WORDTAG O First
16 WORDTAG O fact
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Midwest
5 WORDTAG O freight
5 WORDTAG I-PER Carter
89 WORDTAG O team
7 WORDTAG I-PER MaliVai
7 WORDTAG O accompanied
56 WORDTAG O Men
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Liverpool
9 WORDTAG O markka
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tommy
7 WORDTAG I-ORG All
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonilla
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Alkmaar
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Cuba
27 WORDTAG O nearly
7 WORDTAG O prayers
11 WORDTAG O first-half
31 WORDTAG O series
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Legia
6 WORDTAG O packed
20 WORDTAG O coalition
5 WORDTAG O adopted
11 WORDTAG I-PER Boardman
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ruutel
7 WORDTAG O original
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Oxford
12 WORDTAG O You
7 WORDTAG O sharp
14 WORDTAG O interim
5 WORDTAG O unbeaten
5 WORDTAG I-PER Reiffel
128 WORDTAG O all
105 WORDTAG O through
8 WORDTAG O inches
18 WORDTAG O officer
7 WORDTAG O journalists
15 WORDTAG O efforts
55 WORDTAG I-PER Michael
20 WORDTAG O AND
5 WORDTAG O short-term
7 WORDTAG O wage
5 WORDTAG O sheet
5 WORDTAG O cutting
29 WORDTAG O groups
5 WORDTAG O mines
11 WORDTAG O marks
10 WORDTAG O loan
93 WORDTAG I-LOC LONDON
5 WORDTAG O sure
5 WORDTAG O prospect
16 WORDTAG I-ORG City
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kocinski
59 WORDTAG O what
8 WORDTAG O accepted
105 WORDTAG O made
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Rotterdam
9 WORDTAG O 7-3
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosnia
12 WORDTAG I-PER Waugh
8 WORDTAG O postponed
74 WORDTAG O due
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Classic
6 WORDTAG I-MISC WORLD
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Collstrop
31 WORDTAG O received
9 WORDTAG O assembly
11 WORDTAG I-ORG (
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Plymouth
30 WORDTAG O immediately
31 WORDTAG O come
11 WORDTAG O monitors
8 WORDTAG O Soyoil
34 WORDTAG O Aug
18 WORDTAG O board
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rodriguez
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
53 WORDTAG O net
21 WORDTAG O profits
6 WORDTAG O Also
9 WORDTAG O population
18 WORDTAG O hope
6 WORDTAG I-ORG SK
29 WORDTAG O trip
68 WORDTAG O champion
17 WORDTAG O battle
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Francisco
7 WORDTAG O margin
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Turkey
19 WORDTAG O member
8 WORDTAG I-ORG AZ
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Serbia
7 WORDTAG O ensure
6 WORDTAG O pursuit
12 WORDTAG O spending
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Internet
22 WORDTAG O turned
5 WORDTAG I-PER Zinzan
6 WORDTAG O 3-2
6 WORDTAG O turnover
5 WORDTAG I-PER Donovan
30 WORDTAG O point
44 WORDTAG O closed
16 WORDTAG O medical
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Federal
5 WORDTAG O destitute
6 WORDTAG O briefly
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Le
7 WORDTAG O propaganda
6 WORDTAG I-PER Thomson
18 WORDTAG O murder
9 WORDTAG I-PER Angel
28 WORDTAG O analysts
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Feyenoord
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem
9 WORDTAG O shipments
50 WORDTAG O sales
10 WORDTAG O fly
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southend
6 WORDTAG O supporting
11 WORDTAG O real
136 WORDTAG O between
9 WORDTAG I-PER Woodbridge
71 WORDTAG O international
1095 WORDTAG O was
8 WORDTAG O goalkeeper
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNESOTA
29 WORDTAG O forecast
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Palestinian
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Athletics
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Betaseron
8 WORDTAG O Just
10 WORDTAG O build
7 WORDTAG O normal
24 WORDTAG O Net
5 WORDTAG O piece
44 WORDTAG O higher
8 WORDTAG O neighbours
6 WORDTAG O distance
43 WORDTAG I-ORG Bank
7 WORDTAG O policies
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Jordan
38 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.
43 WORDTAG O began
6 WORDTAG I-PER Edgar
71 WORDTAG O final
16 WORDTAG O states
11 WORDTAG O above
17 WORDTAG O twice
7362 WORDTAG O .
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kennedy
19 WORDTAG O 51
5 WORDTAG O medicine
32 WORDTAG O possible
38 WORDTAG O recent
34 WORDTAG O 59
22 WORDTAG O cost
5 WORDTAG O lions
6 WORDTAG B-ORG FDP
8 WORDTAG O rescued
16 WORDTAG O situation
5 WORDTAG O normally
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Nancy
22 WORDTAG O dead
20 WORDTAG O 542
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
14 WORDTAG O anything
11 WORDTAG O improve
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
6 WORDTAG I-LOC HELSINKI
8 WORDTAG O names
14 WORDTAG O cases
14 WORDTAG I-PER Craig
16 WORDTAG O felt
10 WORDTAG O film
9 WORDTAG O solution
5 WORDTAG O accusing
8 WORDTAG O comments
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Angeles
39 WORDTAG O Police
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brush
6 WORDTAG O .504
11 WORDTAG O university
6 WORDTAG I-MISC ITALIAN
9 WORDTAG O spend
12 WORDTAG I-LOC North
19 WORDTAG I-PER Aamir
8 WORDTAG O outlook
945 WORDTAG O 0
8 WORDTAG O agents
7 WORDTAG I-LOC National
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Colorado
44 WORDTAG O 23
14 WORDTAG O truce
5 WORDTAG O muscle
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Republican
7 WORDTAG O equipment
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Five
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Montreal
7 WORDTAG I-ORG JC
7 WORDTAG I-PER Popov
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cozma
7 WORDTAG O helicopter
11 WORDTAG O =
5 WORDTAG I-MISC GTR
17 WORDTAG O your
15 WORDTAG I-PER Marcelo
5 WORDTAG O mutual
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tauziat
5 WORDTAG O holds
106 WORDTAG O did
53 WORDTAG O get
9 WORDTAG O unions
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sittard
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Chechens
58 WORDTAG O runs
10 WORDTAG I-PER Benjamin
5 WORDTAG O dispute
10 WORDTAG O crash
24 WORDTAG I-ORG Association
6 WORDTAG O surrender
22 WORDTAG I-ORG NATO
106 WORDTAG O day
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bogra
6 WORDTAG I-ORG .
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ballanger
6 WORDTAG O probe
7 WORDTAG O else
19 WORDTAG O teams
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Raith
11 WORDTAG O opposed
7 WORDTAG O fled
10 WORDTAG O alliance
12 WORDTAG I-ORG OM
20 WORDTAG O always
8 WORDTAG O envoy
6 WORDTAG I-PER Moura
7 WORDTAG O reforms
9 WORDTAG O delegates
11 WORDTAG O born
8 WORDTAG O formal
17 WORDTAG O aircraft
12 WORDTAG O daughter
40 WORDTAG O 63
501 WORDTAG O have
17 WORDTAG O gains
9 WORDTAG O mine
15 WORDTAG O serious
100 WORDTAG O where
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Dow
16 WORDTAG O community
11 WORDTAG O bodies
40 WORDTAG O current
31 WORDTAG O face
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Humenne
72 WORDTAG O so
5 WORDTAG O 1949
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Nazi
5 WORDTAG O 38th
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Moscow
6 WORDTAG O understanding
11 WORDTAG O below
10 WORDTAG O huge
10 WORDTAG O victim
330 WORDTAG O which
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Madrid
40 WORDTAG O budget
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Jewish
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombo
6 WORDTAG O blame
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Luxembourg
23 WORDTAG O striker
55 WORDTAG O good
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Utrecht
11 WORDTAG B-LOC _INITCAP_
18 WORDTAG O electoral
26 WORDTAG I-MISC OPEN
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jones
16 WORDTAG O special
19 WORDTAG I-PER Sanchez
7 WORDTAG O threats
46 WORDTAG O fell
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
10 WORDTAG I-PER Lee
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
6 WORDTAG O administrative
6 WORDTAG I-MISC RUGBY
6 WORDTAG I-ORG EPR
97 WORDTAG O n't
17 WORDTAG O 41
106 WORDTAG O just
6 WORDTAG O halt
18 WORDTAG O 38
25 WORDTAG I-MISC Chinese
25 WORDTAG O attacks
8 WORDTAG O DIV
42 WORDTAG O quarter
6 WORDTAG O chances
13 WORDTAG O However
2789 WORDTAG O and
199 WORDTAG O told
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Nigeria
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Greece
5 WORDTAG I-PER Natalya
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Promodes
6 WORDTAG O bringing
15 WORDTAG O hard
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Kong
20 WORDTAG O stay
28 WORDTAG O exports
12 WORDTAG O every
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardinals
121 WORDTAG O Minister
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Estonia
7 WORDTAG O items
11 WORDTAG O mln
5 WORDTAG O Not
6 WORDTAG O reputation
9 WORDTAG O 1.5
17 WORDTAG O survey
7 WORDTAG O Squad
22 WORDTAG O committee
5 WORDTAG I-PER Irina
9 WORDTAG O ready
5 WORDTAG O bounce
122 WORDTAG I-LOC France
8 WORDTAG I-PER Simitis
8 WORDTAG O calling
11 WORDTAG O training
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Washington
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
13 WORDTAG O religious
31 WORDTAG O She
32 WORDTAG O tabulate
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Cologne
23 WORDTAG O bid
68 WORDTAG O 25
66 WORDTAG O says
7 WORDTAG O quarterly
9 WORDTAG O travelling
5 WORDTAG I-ORG General
7 WORDTAG O politics
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bremen
10 WORDTAG O hotel
7 WORDTAG O controls
10 WORDTAG I-LOC ATHENS
12 WORDTAG O 6-5
75 WORDTAG O 6-1
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Charlton
10 WORDTAG I-PER Saddam
5 WORDTAG O thrown
11 WORDTAG O subject
6 WORDTAG O space
6 WORDTAG I-PER Berger
6 WORDTAG O hostages
13 WORDTAG O foot
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Air
8 WORDTAG O 8,000
10 WORDTAG O cause
6 WORDTAG O compensation
9 WORDTAG I-PER Agassi
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Finance
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
10 WORDTAG O flights
9 WORDTAG O successful
7 WORDTAG O 1996-08-21
6 WORDTAG O Shr
10 WORDTAG O billions
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costa
7 WORDTAG O attended
57 WORDTAG O race
9 WORDTAG I-PER Olsza
5 WORDTAG O 129
16 WORDTAG O 20,000
11 WORDTAG O assets
32 WORDTAG O reports
31 WORDTAG O brought
8 WORDTAG I-PER Antonio
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Oakland
5 WORDTAG O establish
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Arab
7 WORDTAG O judicial
6 WORDTAG O m
5 WORDTAG O anniversary
6 WORDTAG O relatively
23 WORDTAG I-MISC Sudanese
7 WORDTAG O .531
12 WORDTAG O ambassador
19 WORDTAG I-PER Meri
6 WORDTAG O option
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Hyundai
34 WORDTAG O tennis
58 WORDTAG I-ORG _RARE_
5 WORDTAG O palace
8 WORDTAG O elect
106 WORDTAG O games
30 WORDTAG O 48
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Huddersfield
8 WORDTAG O monthly
6 WORDTAG I-PER Shimon
8 WORDTAG O Six
143 WORDTAG O market
207 WORDTAG O It
5 WORDTAG O eventually
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rifkind
8 WORDTAG O 15-8
52 WORDTAG O going
21 WORDTAG O dealers
10 WORDTAG O crude
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Sakai
9 WORDTAG O ballot
83 WORDTAG O earlier
17 WORDTAG O separatist
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
10 WORDTAG O begun
14 WORDTAG O ending
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanwha
14 WORDTAG O export
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
6 WORDTAG O Dividend
19 WORDTAG I-PER R.
1243 WORDTAG O -
9 WORDTAG O rises
5 WORDTAG O sweeping
17 WORDTAG O telephone
10 WORDTAG O GDP
6 WORDTAG O 170
525 WORDTAG O be
33 WORDTAG I-ORG York
10 WORDTAG O heroin
8 WORDTAG O lives
7 WORDTAG O active
17 WORDTAG O port
17 WORDTAG O deals
10 WORDTAG O confidence
33 WORDTAG O April
11 WORDTAG O suspect
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Moenchengladbach
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ING
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MILWAUKEE
14 WORDTAG O surgery
7 WORDTAG O lifting
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alesi
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Orioles
10 WORDTAG O add
20 WORDTAG O 1990
8 WORDTAG O edged
8 WORDTAG O removed
7 WORDTAG I-PER Alberto
6 WORDTAG O birds
18 WORDTAG O child
6 WORDTAG O themselves
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Baghdad
14 WORDTAG O NOTE
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tennis
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Houston
7 WORDTAG O lbw
14 WORDTAG I-ORG North
5 WORDTAG O nurses
11 WORDTAG I-MISC 1,000
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Nations
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Investors
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Serb
12 WORDTAG O 78
5 WORDTAG O genocide
50 WORDTAG O economic
5 WORDTAG O 278
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Central
14 WORDTAG O pulled
52 WORDTAG O agency
10 WORDTAG O appointed
53 WORDTAG O late
21 WORDTAG I-PER Mother
11 WORDTAG O heard
10 WORDTAG O documents
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Zenith
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ferguson
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Doboj
9 WORDTAG O mainly
7 WORDTAG O waste
15 WORDTAG I-PER Weizman
13 WORDTAG O 2-2
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
9 WORDTAG O insurance
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Sri
70 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsroom
124 WORDTAG O officials
6 WORDTAG O 1988
13 WORDTAG O trader
5 WORDTAG O profit-taking
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gianluca
5 WORDTAG O directly
24 WORDTAG O source
14 WORDTAG O done
6 WORDTAG O repeat
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johnny
335 WORDTAG O beat
16 WORDTAG I-PER Chang
6 WORDTAG O .543
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Lakes
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Corporation
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Scotland
6 WORDTAG O 15.
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Denmark
7 WORDTAG O catch
12 WORDTAG O WORLD
8 WORDTAG O establishment
14 WORDTAG I-PER Boris
110 WORDTAG O next
17 WORDTAG O par
5 WORDTAG I-LOC St.
14 WORDTAG O starting
44 WORDTAG O 65
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hill
5 WORDTAG O civilian
24 WORDTAG O big
5 WORDTAG O acts
7 WORDTAG O democratic
6 WORDTAG O except
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
8 WORDTAG O happened
10 WORDTAG O waiting
21 WORDTAG O seized
18 WORDTAG I-PER Rubin
9 WORDTAG O missionaries
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Albanian
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Coast
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlantic
14 WORDTAG I-PER Graham
27 WORDTAG O rule
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bucharest
117 WORDTAG O four
9 WORDTAG I-PER Takeda
6 WORDTAG O credit
52 WORDTAG O 73
5 WORDTAG O Fastest
15 WORDTAG O hour
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tirana
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Ethiopia
38 WORDTAG O total
8 WORDTAG O volatility
7 WORDTAG O red
6 WORDTAG O 30th
47 WORDTAG O central
9 WORDTAG O council
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Health
7 WORDTAG O claims
10 WORDTAG I-PER Corser
7 WORDTAG O knee
26 WORDTAG O One
12 WORDTAG O Sales
25 WORDTAG O course
23 WORDTAG I-PER Alexander
35 WORDTAG O cut
7 WORDTAG O bullish
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rocca
57 WORDTAG O goals
5 WORDTAG O heavily
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Council
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Neths
21 WORDTAG O 36
5 WORDTAG O independent
6 WORDTAG O experience
30 WORDTAG I-ORG YORK
972 WORDTAG O 2
36 WORDTAG O fourth
5 WORDTAG O sentences
50 WORDTAG O taking
9 WORDTAG I-PER Costas
5 WORDTAG I-ORG LTTE
11 WORDTAG O county
7 WORDTAG O linking
13 WORDTAG O thousands
6 WORDTAG I-ORG PTT
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Linz
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jean
8 WORDTAG I-PER Darren
21 WORDTAG O guilders
13 WORDTAG O ?
45 WORDTAG I-ORG Commission
12 WORDTAG O weekly
6 WORDTAG O trends
5 WORDTAG O +7095
36 WORDTAG O help
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Pakistani
7 WORDTAG O instead
5 WORDTAG I-PER Vacek
17 WORDTAG O spokeswoman
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Faulding
17 WORDTAG O goods
8 WORDTAG O presidency
24 WORDTAG O leg
5 WORDTAG I-LOC TIRANA
10 WORDTAG O cars
9 WORDTAG O representatives
14 WORDTAG O streak
12 WORDTAG O freed
8 WORDTAG O Rating
78 WORDTAG I-MISC British
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayer
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Sheffield
16 WORDTAG O Bowling
43 WORDTAG O decision
5 WORDTAG O seasons
7 WORDTAG O disappointed
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Golf
6 WORDTAG B-ORG PDS
7 WORDTAG O stadium
31 WORDTAG I-LOC Kenya
14 WORDTAG O 33
7 WORDTAG O flow
30 WORDTAG I-ORG NEW
13 WORDTAG O sanctions
45 WORDTAG O weeks
6 WORDTAG I-PER Bruguera
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vermont
5 WORDTAG O profitable
13 WORDTAG O ransom
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqi
9 WORDTAG O registered
16 WORDTAG O whole
9 WORDTAG I-PER Perot
7 WORDTAG I-MISC TOUR
8 WORDTAG O runner-up
9 WORDTAG O registrations
24 WORDTAG O great
6 WORDTAG O Latest
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
15 WORDTAG I-PER Gore
5 WORDTAG O AS
6 WORDTAG O colony
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul
5 WORDTAG O coup
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Rally
6 WORDTAG O 33rd
132 WORDTAG O other
10 WORDTAG O kg
12 WORDTAG O abandoned
16 WORDTAG I-PER Juan
7 WORDTAG O speed
5 WORDTAG O batsman
186 WORDTAG O or
22 WORDTAG O volume
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ekeus
6 WORDTAG O atmosphere
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bernard
10 WORDTAG O kill
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
70 WORDTAG O victory
5 WORDTAG I-PER Montgomerie
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Strasbourg
9 WORDTAG I-PER Owens
7 WORDTAG O store
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Groningen
21 WORDTAG O really
6 WORDTAG O bronze
8 WORDTAG O activities
5 WORDTAG O span
15 WORDTAG O often
6 WORDTAG O factor
5 WORDTAG O re-election
7 WORDTAG O World
31 WORDTAG O used
8 WORDTAG O Now
8 WORDTAG I-ORG SPLA
104 WORDTAG O 12
34 WORDTAG I-ORG 's
284 WORDTAG O this
5 WORDTAG O Socialist
11 WORDTAG O towns
7 WORDTAG O flying
12 WORDTAG O MATCH
19 WORDTAG O arms
7 WORDTAG O Ambassador
29 WORDTAG O 0-0
64 WORDTAG O 5.
7 WORDTAG I-PER Habsudova
11 WORDTAG O spoke
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
19 WORDTAG O caught
7 WORDTAG O actions
10 WORDTAG O ends
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Florida
27 WORDTAG O times
114 WORDTAG O because
6 WORDTAG I-PER Banisadr
20 WORDTAG I-ORG International
7 WORDTAG O 5-2
99 WORDTAG O July
20 WORDTAG O double
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Los
21 WORDTAG O settlement
9 WORDTAG O Cash
11 WORDTAG O posted
74 WORDTAG O saying
17 WORDTAG O attempt
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TEXAS
7 WORDTAG O sea
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Expos
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cannes
22 WORDTAG O defeat
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fleurian
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Taibe
59 WORDTAG O ago
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Minnesota
17 WORDTAG O leaving
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlanta
8 WORDTAG I-MISC New
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stevanin
7 WORDTAG I-LOC AKRON
6 WORDTAG O TITLE
5 WORDTAG O farms
105 WORDTAG O win
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Pirates
35 WORDTAG O disease
29 WORDTAG O latest
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Singapore
11 WORDTAG O living
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Catholic
8 WORDTAG O offers
124 WORDTAG O group
19 WORDTAG I-PER Brady
6 WORDTAG O specified
117 WORDTAG O 6-4
5 WORDTAG O .469
5 WORDTAG I-PER Azharuddin
10 WORDTAG O 176
19 WORDTAG O legal
24 WORDTAG O economy
214 WORDTAG O also
22 WORDTAG O tax
24 WORDTAG O Result
17 WORDTAG O BEAT
41 WORDTAG O leading
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chemlon
33 WORDTAG O strong
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Motorola
9 WORDTAG O opponents
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Java
7 WORDTAG O solo
74 WORDTAG O end
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloria
6 WORDTAG O sharply
38 WORDTAG I-LOC York
75 WORDTAG O capital
689 WORDTAG O is
11 WORDTAG O consecutive
11 WORDTAG I-PER Atherton
14 WORDTAG O join
9 WORDTAG I-PER Haga
7 WORDTAG O specific
8 WORDTAG I-PER Masterkova
7 WORDTAG I-ORG S&P
8 WORDTAG I-MISC US$
33 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurdish
19 WORDTAG O girl
46 WORDTAG O 1-0
6 WORDTAG O reopened
5 WORDTAG O outcome
7 WORDTAG O ------------------------
6 WORDTAG O LATEST
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kohl
7 WORDTAG O pull
7 WORDTAG O pain
12 WORDTAG O diplomats
86 WORDTAG O They
7 WORDTAG I-PER Terry
26 WORDTAG O struck
6 WORDTAG I-MISC UEFA
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Briton
7 WORDTAG O decisions
17 WORDTAG I-ORG CITY
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Organisation
7 WORDTAG I-ORG de
5 WORDTAG O tense
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Vale
6 WORDTAG I-ORG CSU
6 WORDTAG O self-rule
50 WORDTAG O arrested
7 WORDTAG O WEDNESDAY
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Monaco
9 WORDTAG O individual
6 WORDTAG O Spot
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Helibor
9 WORDTAG I-MISC PRIX
60 WORDTAG O meet
117 WORDTAG O six
63 WORDTAG O 24
9 WORDTAG O junior
11 WORDTAG O riots
23 WORDTAG O 7-4
15 WORDTAG O To
6 WORDTAG O united
53 WORDTAG O northern
5 WORDTAG O lows
54 WORDTAG O May
11 WORDTAG O worked
471 WORDTAG O after
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Newcastle
12 WORDTAG O computer
5 WORDTAG O MOTOR
11 WORDTAG I-ORG House
21 WORDTAG I-PER Todd
19 WORDTAG O 57
15 WORDTAG I-PER Morris
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NEC
7 WORDTAG O criminal
14 WORDTAG O Jul
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Europe
36 WORDTAG O failed
6 WORDTAG O extended
9 WORDTAG O kills
7221 WORDTAG O the
6 WORDTAG O satisfied
14 WORDTAG O fiscal
98 WORDTAG O if
5 WORDTAG O developments
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Iranian
5 WORDTAG O 10.5
25 WORDTAG O letter
10 WORDTAG O suit
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Havre
19 WORDTAG O francs
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Sydney
15 WORDTAG I-ORG FRANCISCO
5 WORDTAG O congress
7 WORDTAG O Baseball
7 WORDTAG O settled
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nobel
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Doetinchem
5 WORDTAG O gestures
7 WORDTAG O prosecutor
57 WORDTAG O bank
5 WORDTAG O reimbursement
15 WORDTAG O Last
5 WORDTAG O tanks
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshoppers
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Institute
5 WORDTAG O ]
11 WORDTAG O lack
41 WORDTAG O fighting
16 WORDTAG I-PER William
20 WORDTAG O February
8 WORDTAG O major-league
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottinghamshire
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Party
71 WORDTAG O you
5 WORDTAG O crowds
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bamerindus
57 WORDTAG I-LOC States
25 WORDTAG O sell
7 WORDTAG O bread
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Delhi
8 WORDTAG O rand
24 WORDTAG O returned
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Rican
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BUENOS
5 WORDTAG I-PER Yihye
6 WORDTAG O directed
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Miss
10 WORDTAG I-PER Machado
8 WORDTAG O extremely
5 WORDTAG O printed
5 WORDTAG O 3/4
12 WORDTAG O contact
6 WORDTAG O engineering
14 WORDTAG O bill
157 WORDTAG O some
50 WORDTAG I-PER John
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Milwaukee
7 WORDTAG O rains
30 WORDTAG O injured
6 WORDTAG O grounds
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Astros
13 WORDTAG O 15-12
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Radio
6 WORDTAG O inch
12 WORDTAG O whom
5 WORDTAG I-LOC JYVASKYLA
11 WORDTAG O table
19 WORDTAG O saw
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tottenham
7 WORDTAG O stayed
40 WORDTAG O side
9 WORDTAG O 150
13 WORDTAG I-ORG University
5 WORDTAG O sealed
19 WORDTAG I-PER Scott
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mitsubishi
92 WORDTAG O seconds
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Lyon
5 WORDTAG O rankings
6 WORDTAG O fatal
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Surabaya
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hasina
20 WORDTAG O staff
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Australia
5 WORDTAG O drivers
5 WORDTAG O imported
7 WORDTAG O regular
12 WORDTAG O allegations
5 WORDTAG O 9/16
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Waalwijk
6 WORDTAG O mate
27 WORDTAG O pound
16 WORDTAG O annual
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqis
40 WORDTAG O STANDINGS
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Hospital
30 WORDTAG O showed
930 WORDTAG O at
99 WORDTAG O September
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Braves
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dynamo
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jacques
5 WORDTAG O factory
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Lotte
5 WORDTAG O returns
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Arabia
5 WORDTAG O END
25 WORDTAG O opened
6 WORDTAG O targets
10 WORDTAG O potential
5 WORDTAG O Since
8 WORDTAG O try
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anthony
5 WORDTAG O falls
5 WORDTAG O belonging
5 WORDTAG O matter
6 WORDTAG O technical
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Seattle
5 WORDTAG O trend
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bobby
29 WORDTAG O use
12 WORDTAG I-PER Asif
6 WORDTAG O follows
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Budapest
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pol
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lancashire
14 WORDTAG O impact
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trinidad
32 WORDTAG O seed
6 WORDTAG I-LOC LISBON
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wang
29 WORDTAG O each
8 WORDTAG O prospects
9 WORDTAG O onto
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ripken
13 WORDTAG O defeated
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mostostal
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ferrigato
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Barnsley
55 WORDTAG O FIRST
10 WORDTAG O ..
176 WORDTAG O people
8 WORDTAG O 24th
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chamorro
6 WORDTAG O formed
28 WORDTAG O holiday
56 WORDTAG O Prime
6 WORDTAG O award
8 WORDTAG O parts
11 WORDTAG O improved
14 WORDTAG O 6.0
11 WORDTAG O challenge
12 WORDTAG O suspended
11 WORDTAG I-PER Irani
15 WORDTAG I-PER Peres
44 WORDTAG O general
24 WORDTAG O needed
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Parma
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rennes
18 WORDTAG O exchange
12 WORDTAG I-PER Patrick
5 WORDTAG O fairly
37 WORDTAG O vote
111 WORDTAG O 1996-08-26
5 WORDTAG O Add
15 WORDTAG O described
5 WORDTAG O 11-6
23 WORDTAG O W
17 WORDTAG O along
33 WORDTAG O press
21 WORDTAG O 400
5 WORDTAG O gathered
5 WORDTAG I-PER Els
44 WORDTAG I-PER Dole
33 WORDTAG O yet
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Pittsburgh
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Twente
5 WORDTAG O thanks
767 WORDTAG O that
20 WORDTAG O January
31 WORDTAG O TENNIS
5 WORDTAG O retail
11 WORDTAG O alleged
5 WORDTAG O gives
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hogg
24 WORDTAG O flight
6 WORDTAG O auctions
6 WORDTAG I-PER Gujral
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bonn
8 WORDTAG I-ORG UNION
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hakkinen
29 WORDTAG O contract
33 WORDTAG O public
7 WORDTAG I-ORG St.
5 WORDTAG I-LOC CLEVELAND
5 WORDTAG O ARA
11 WORDTAG O operating
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Genoa
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Insurance
8 WORDTAG O voted
17 WORDTAG O demanding
23 WORDTAG O Played
7 WORDTAG O postpone
5 WORDTAG I-PER Anton
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Hong
7 WORDTAG O yesterday
55 WORDTAG O 75
94 WORDTAG I-MISC Cup
6 WORDTAG O remote
10 WORDTAG O epidemic
6 WORDTAG O command
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Slam
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ata-ur-Rehman
5 WORDTAG O rated
53 WORDTAG O plan
8 WORDTAG O revenue
5 WORDTAG O maintained
5 WORDTAG O artillery
85 WORDTAG O Results
5 WORDTAG O mistakes
10 WORDTAG O Government
9 WORDTAG O cargo
5 WORDTAG O praised
8 WORDTAG O fob
10 WORDTAG O bilateral
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anders
6 WORDTAG O weapon
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Austria
9 WORDTAG I-PER Ronald
9 WORDTAG O example
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interior
89 WORDTAG O month
6 WORDTAG I-PER Akam
16 WORDTAG O a.m.
5 WORDTAG O exiled
9 WORDTAG O cement
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
5 WORDTAG I-MISC LAKES
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frankie
8 WORDTAG O begins
10 WORDTAG O intervention
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Western
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yorkshire
8 WORDTAG I-PER Perry
24 WORDTAG O denied
5 WORDTAG I-PER Brandes
32 WORDTAG O markets
9 WORDTAG O vehicles
5 WORDTAG O arm
7 WORDTAG O 90th
5 WORDTAG O nominee
7 WORDTAG O various
5 WORDTAG I-ORG East
9 WORDTAG O two-run
9 WORDTAG O right-wing
63 WORDTAG I-LOC Israel
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Bulgaria
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Tennis
12 WORDTAG O 4-1
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Indians
8 WORDTAG O winter
58 WORDTAG O newspaper
12 WORDTAG I-ORG American
6 WORDTAG O article
17 WORDTAG I-LOC San
6 WORDTAG O 13th
6 WORDTAG O DRAW
7 WORDTAG O via
22 WORDTAG O deficit
19 WORDTAG O November
5 WORDTAG I-PER Barry
15 WORDTAG O list
5 WORDTAG O 398
17 WORDTAG O husband
5 WORDTAG I-PER Klinsmann
6 WORDTAG B-ORG SPD
19 WORDTAG O rupees
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Wimbledon
5 WORDTAG O trained
6 WORDTAG O lb
89 WORDTAG O v
130 WORDTAG I-LOC Australia
14 WORDTAG O stake
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Canada
5 WORDTAG I-MISC ADRs
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackburn
22 WORDTAG O player
5 WORDTAG O replaced
12 WORDTAG I-PER Pedro
71 WORDTAG O 22
7 WORDTAG O representative
6 WORDTAG O sparked
7 WORDTAG O identified
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Austrian
5 WORDTAG I-ORG JavaSoft
9 WORDTAG O sees
